去他媽的金剛狼
Fuck Wolverine.
首先 他是因為看到《死侍1》火了 才把《金剛狼3》也拍成R級的
First, he rides my coattails with the R rating.
其次是這個多毛畜生用死這招來提升電影層次
Then the hairy motherfucker ups the ante by dying.
真是個混蛋
What a dick.
你猜怎麼著 小狼狼?
Well, guess what, Wolvie?
不光你會死 哥也會
I'm dying in this one, too.
想知道為什麼我要在1200加侖的
To understand why I took a cat-nap
高質燃料上打個小盹
on 1,200 gallons of high-test fuel...
得從六周前的
I need to take you back
露水坡說起
to the dewy slopes of six weeks ago.
我的英雄事業已經走向國際化了
I'd gone international,
跟超多殺人犯和黑幫暴徒對著干
taking out mass murderers, gangsters,
還有那些不可言說的怪物
unspeakable monsters.
那種除了我 沒人敢碰的大佬
People nobody would touch. Except me.
我要那些被我碰的人爽到極點
I'm gonna touch them all over.
嘿 我是蓋爾
Hey, it's Gail calling.
特喜歡你閃閃發光的外套
Love the shiny suit.
很襯你那
Really brings out
性販運罪犯的眼神
the sex trafficker in your eyes.
我聽不懂廣東話 這位...先生
I don't speak Cantonese, Mister...
蒙我都懶得蒙
Well, I'm not even gonna attempt that.
但我八年級的時候確實選修過西班牙語 所以
But I did take 8th grade Spanish, so...
翻譯過來就是
Which literally translates to...
我從不討價還價 你個混球
I don't bargain, pumpkin fucker.
一 二 三 四
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro...
我要來一杯蔓越莓-西柚伏特加
I'll take a cranberry-grapefruit vodka.
我知道這就是所謂的海風伏特加
I know it's called a Sea Breeze.
別逼我說出來
Don't make me say it.
放音樂吧 小可愛
Hit it, Dolly.
成功奪走下罪犯們拿槍的手
Taking the hands out of the guns of the criminals!
真不該進來
Whoo! Do not go in there!
媽呀 我的媽呀 暫停 趕緊暫停
Oh, God! Oh, God, time out! Time out!
停 這幫混蛋的血都濺到我眼睛裡了
Cut. Got bad guy blood, right in my open eye.
真是太惡心了
Oh, that's so gross.
我去
Fuck.
你是童子軍團長凱文嗎
Scoutmaster Kevin?
太騷了嗎?
Too exotic?
我的環球正義之行的最終任務
My world tour brought me home
就是回到家干掉這個人 謝爾蓋·瓦力什尼科夫
to this guy, Sergei Valishnikov.
不過我們待會兒再聊他
But we'll get to him in a moment.
因為我知道你在想什麼
'Cause I know what you're thinking.
"幸好我沒帶孩子來看這電影"
"I'm so glad I left the kiddos at home."
但是你這就不對了
But that's where you'd be wrong.
你的保姆這個時候已經嗑藥嗑到嗨了
That babysitter of yours is high as fuck right now...
而且不管你信不信 死侍2 是一部合家歡電影
and, believe it or not, Deadpool 2 is a family film.
真的 不騙你
True story.
一部好的合家歡電影通常都是從凶殘的謀殺開始的
And every good family film starts with a vicious murder.
比如《小鹿斑比》《獅子王》《電鋸驚魂7》
Bambi, The Lion King, Saw 7.
我勒個老天呀  那家伙著火了
Holy shit pickles! That guy's on fire.
那不是特效啊 伙計們 他是真的著火了 沒錯
That's not CGI, folks. He's actually on fire.
你們知道有人出錢給我殺壞人的 對吧？
Yeah. You know I get paid to take out bad guys, right?
但這個人
But this guy?
他是壞人裡最壞的那一個
He was one of the worst of 'em.
趕緊把這破門給我打開
Hurry up and open this fucking door,
我們一起殺了這個混蛋
and let's kill this motherfucker!
呃 惡心死了
Ugh. So gross.
居然進安全屋？有用嗎？
A panic room? Really?
你能出來讓我宰一下嗎
Can you come out?
我真的得走了 今天是我的紀念日
I really have to go. It's my anniversary.
我一次次地聽到人們說
Over and over, I hear people say,
"我就是不夠自信"
"I just don't have enough confidence."
聽著 自信不是你生來就有的
Listen, confidence is not something you have.
是要你自己去創造的
It's something you create.
而且你什麼時候都能去創造它
And you can create it at any moment in time.
自信不過就是人自己
A sense of confidence is nothing
內在的一種力量
but a sense of power within yourself...
一種能確定自己可以做成某事的力量
a sense of certainty that you can pull something off.
快他媽開車啊 快他媽的開車啊
Start the car! Start the fucking car!
多芬德
Dopinder!
快他媽的開車啊
Start the fucking car!
嚇得我屎都出來了
- Whoo! - Oh, I shit my pants.
事實上 拉褲子的人可能是我
Actually, that may have been me.
任務完成了?
Oh, mission accomplished?
呃 跟小布什一樣沒完成
Well, in a George W. sort of way.
那個混蛋不可能永遠躲在安全屋裡不出來的
Fucker can't stay in a panic room forever.
你已經是活在夢裡了 死侍
Oh, you're living the dreams, DP.
在世界行俠仗義確實很爽 多芬德
It has been quite the run, Dopinder,
誰能想到呢？
and who'da thought?
我現在都能跟耶穌出現在同一句子裡了
Now I'm talked about in the same sentence as Jesus.
R級電影排名第一是《耶穌受難記》 第二就是《死侍》了
Passion of the Christ, then me.
最起碼在國內是這樣的
At least domestically.
但在海外票房上
We beat them overseas,
尤其是在那種不信教的國家 我們把《耶穌受難記》虐爆了
where there's no such thing as religion.
我也想活在夢裡啊 侍侍
I do want to live the dreams, Pool Boy.
開出租車可是一點意思都沒有
Taxiing is not as sexy as it looks.
- 我想要充實我的 - 口袋嗎?
- I want to fill my... - Pockets?
你最想來點什麼？來點白粉？
What's your poison? A little, uh, cokey cokey?
沒在網上買鞋子
Can't maintain an erection
就硬不起來
without buying shoes online?
剛說的那個我也從沒經歷過
I've never experienced that last one.
和我說說吧小可愛
Talk to me, Goose.
我本來想說的是 靈魂 我想要充實自己的靈魂
I was going to say "soul". I want to fill my soul.
我想要找個歸屬 像你一樣 死侍先生
I want to belong to something, like you, Pool, sir.
多芬德
- Dopinder... - Hmm?
你真是一直在給我驚喜啊
You never cease to surprise me.
你的心海真是深邃非凡
You know, the depth of your heart is extraordinary.
我們都需要一種歸屬感
We all need a sense of belonging.
我們都需要一種真正的家的感覺
We all need a genuine sense of home.
某個地方
A place in this world.
我想要成為一名職業殺手
I want to become a contract killer.
我沒聽清 你剛才說什麼？
I'm sorry. What did you say?
還記得我綁架班都
Remember when I kidnapped Bandhu
還威脅要殺了他的時候嗎
and threatened him with great violence?
某種程度上來說已經殺了
You kind of killed him.
還記得《夜訪吸血鬼》那部電影嗎
And then remember the movie Interview with the Vampire?
我並不想記得
Don't want to.
湯姆·克魯斯第一次
When Tom Cruise fed
喂10歲的克爾斯滕·鄧斯特
10-year-old Kirsten Dunst blood
喝血的時候
for the first time...
然後她看向他光滑
and she looked up at his smooth,
英俊的臉
handsome face and said...
說道："我還想要喝"
"I want some more."
啊 侍兒 腦補一下 我就是那個10歲的克爾斯滕·鄧斯特
Oh, Pool, picture me, a 10-year-old Kirsten Dunst.
畫面感太強 想忘都難
I'll never not picture that.
但是我非常想終止這話題
But I can't wait to never speak of this,
越快越好
as soon as possible.
我們到了
We're here.
你是我的湯姆·克魯斯
You're my Tom Cruise!
你是我的克來斯滕·鄧斯特
And you're my Kristen Dunst!
克來斯滕 克爾斯滕
Kristen? Kirsten?
對不起我遲到了
Sorry I'm late.
有一群小孩子困在樹上了
There was a bunch of
我不救他們
handicapable children stuck in a tree...
- 他們就會摔成殘疾的... - 別想蒙我
- and I had to, uh... - Uh-uh.
我剛和蝙蝠俠打了一架
You're right. I was fighting a caped badass.
然後我發現他的媽媽也叫瑪莎
But then we discovered his mom is named Martha, too.
這麼編也蒙不過去
No.
堵車呢？
Traffic?
行嗎？
Hmm?
像你思念我一樣狠狠的親我吧 小賤
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
你過來啊
Well, come here.
我想洗個澡然後脫掉這身衣服
I'm gonna shower and get out of this suit.
你不想要一個驚喜嗎？
Don't you want your surprise?
我看起來像一個燒傷的病患嗎
Do I look like a patient burn victim?
我這給你來個驚喜
I got one for you, too.
周年快樂 寶貝
Happy anniversary, baby.
快打開 快打開
Open, open, open.
滑雪球紀念幣
Skee-Ball token.
我們的第一次約會
Our first date.
對
Yup.
這是貨真價實的高檔鉛
That's genuine, high-grade lead.
我會永遠保存它
I'll keep it forever.
謝謝你 寶貝
Thank you, baby.
- 快拆你的吧 - 好吧
- Open yours. - All right, all right.
這是
Oh...
這是我所見過的最漂亮的
That's just the most beautiful thing that I've...
我不知道這是什麼東西
I don't know what this is.
我的宮內節育器
My IUD.
是炸彈嗎？
A bomb?
不是 你個精蟲上腦的傻瓜 這是我的節育器
No, dick for brains. My birth control device.
你說是你的
What, you mean that your...
產子計劃正式啟動
Baby factory's open for business.
哦 我的天吶
Oh, my God!
哦 我的老天爺 我想要一個男孩
Oh, my God! I want a boy!
或者一個女孩 不管是哪個我都喜歡
Or a little girl! Definitely one or the other!
我想讓我們的孩子只有名不要姓
Oh! And I want our kid to have only one name.
例如切麗 或者托德
Like Cher or Todd.
你要先播種啊 大傻瓜
You gotta pump a baby in me first, cowboy.
我會的
Yes, I do.
我們先看點黃片 然後看誰才是床上的霸主
Let's watch some porn and show that bed who's boss.
就這麼定了
Let's do that.
這首歌你聽起來耳熟嗎
Does this song sound familiar to you?
梅
May.
如果是男孩 就叫康恩 女孩就叫梅
Connor, if it's a boy. May, if it's a girl.
感覺真怪啊
So weird.
家庭這個詞對我來說一直都是髒話
Family was always an F-word to me.
混蛋父親拿著東西跑了...
My pile of shit father took off and bailed.
我沒有好的父輩告訴我該怎麼做才能
I mean, it's not like I have a lot of strong role models
當好托德的爹
to draw off of for Todd.
嘿 看著我
Hey. Look at me.
你不是你的父親
You are not your father.
另外
Besides...
我永遠 永遠都不會 讓我們的孩子叫托德
I will never, ever let our child be named Todd.
但是問題是
But here's the thing,
難道故事不是這樣發展的嗎
isn't that how it always works?
就像星戰裡
Like in Star Wars,
男人注定會成為他們的父親
men are destined to become their father...
然後和他們的姐姐來一場兩廂情願的啪啪啪
and then have consensual sex with their sister?
我覺得你錯過了那電影裡面 很多 很多 的劇情
I think you missed big, big chunks of that movie.
沒有 我確定盧克上了她
No, I'm pretty sure Luke nailed her.
寶貝 那是帝國反擊戰裡的劇情
Baby, that's Empire.
重點是 孩子們
The point is, kids...
他們給我們機會讓我們成為更好的人
they give us a chance to be better than we are.
比我們以前更好
Better than we used to be.
你比我看上去聰明太多了
You're a lot smarter than I look.
我要去做些點心
I'm gonna go make dessert.
你去把小皮鞭准備好 我們來造一個超級寶寶吧
You get the strap-on. Let's make a super baby.
雖然我確定不是這麼一回事 不過可以一試
Pretty sure it doesn't work that way, but we can try.
叫克裡斯托怎麼樣 K開頭
What about Krystal? But with a "K"?
這樣太像脫衣舞娘了
It's too stripper-y.
K開頭的凱文
Kevin with a "K"!
不行 還是太脫衣舞娘了
No, too stripper-y, too.
厄爾
Uh, Earl!
如果我們叫他厄爾
He's gonna go straight to jail
他會直接進監獄的
if we name him Earl.
布魯斯怎麼樣
What about Bruce?
不行
No.
趴下
Get down.
什麼
What?
寶貝兒 寶貝兒
Baby? Baby?
我沒事
I'm okay.
我不用甩塗奶油芝士的餐刀真是太好了
Thank God I didn't have to use the cream cheese spreader.
求求你
Please.
Please. Please.
寶貝 對不起
Baby, I'm so sorry.
不
No!
爸爸 你能聽到我麼
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
只有我這麼覺得嗎
Is it just me, or does
《冰雪奇緣》裡的"你想做個雪人嗎"
Do You Want to Build a Snowman? from Frozen...
聽上去非常像
sound suspiciously like
《燕特爾》的"爸爸 你能聽到我嗎"
Papa, Can You Hear Me? from Yentl?
爸爸 你能聽到我嗎
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
而且沒有人他媽注意到
And nobody fucking realizes it.
回家吧 你已經在這裡呆三天了好嗎
Go home. You've been here for three days, okay?
你臭得像內戰士兵身上爛掉的傷口
You smell like somebody shit in a Civil War wound...
被人再拉了一坨翔在上面
after it had become gangrenous.
他們應該切掉它 干嘛在上面拉屎呢
They should've just amputated it. Why shit in it?
完全解釋不通啊
Doesn't make any sense.
我超愛冰雪奇緣
I love Frozen.
我愛她 我像海洋愛水一樣愛她
I loved her. I loved her like an ocean loves water.
海洋裡都是水啊
An ocean is water.
更重要的是 我好喜歡她 我真的好喜歡她 你懂嗎
More importantly, I liked her. I really liked her, you know?
喬治·邁克爾說得對
George Michael was right.
我再也不會跳舞了 我操
I'm never gonna dance again. Fuck!
他也死了
He's dead, too.
至少我們還有鮑伊
At least we still have Bowie.
我們還有...鮑伊
Yeah. We still have Bowie.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不管你喝了多少杯
Shot after shot,
都不能改變一個事實 就是我覺得你...
it's not gonna change the fact that I think you're...
你在噓噓嗎 你現在在小便嗎
Are you pissing? Are you urinating right now?
你現在在做你小便時的慣用表情
You're making the face that you make when you urinate.
- 他是在噓噓嗎  - 我馬上打掃
- Is he pissing? - I'm on it!
干得不錯 多芬德
There you go, Dopinder.
你想做一個職業殺手
If you want to be a contract killer...
就要在學會用槍之前 先學會用拖把
you gotta handle a mop before you handle a gun.
其實我不太懂它們倆
Although I don't quite understand
到底有什麼相似之處
how they are at all similar.
他們都有手柄啊 現在別煩我
Well, they both have handles. Now, leave me.
回家吧 韋德
Go home, Wade.
我沒有家了 黃哥 我只有...
I don't have a home, Weas, you know. I got a...
操 真的 我沒事了
Fuck! Okay, I'm fine.
我沒事了
I'm fine.
你知道沒事的潛意思是什麼嗎 韋德
You know what "fine" stands for, Wade?
是倒霉 沒安全感 缺乏關愛和情緒波動大
Fucked up, insecure, needy, and emotional.
根據那個
According to the...
- 庫伯勒-羅絲什麼的 - 對
- Kubler-Ross. - Yeah.
對 根據庫伯勒-羅絲模型
According to the Kubler-Ross model...
否認就是喪慟五個階段中的一個
denial is just one of the five stages of grief.
我的天哪 巴克
Jesus Christ, Buck!
你接下來可沒台詞說了
No more speaking lines for you.
我在重新考慮
"I'm thinking it over!"
我滴個親娘啊
Motherfuck!
靠
Fuck!
你他媽來我這干什麼啊
The hell you doin' here?
你不知道什麼叫敲門嗎
Don't you know how to knock?
我以為你看見我了
I thought you saw me...
用你耳朵看的
with your ears.
你是運氣好才沒被我一槍打中...
You're lucky I didn't shoot you in the...
這面牆
The wall?
還是冰箱 我現在好痛苦
The refrigerator? I'm in so much pain.
我聽見新聞了 甜心
I heard the news, sweetie.
我真的非常抱歉 真的
I'm very sorry. I am.
我該怎麼辦啊 阿爾
What am I gonna do, Al?
可能是一些很可怕的事情吧
Probably something terrible.
即使對你來說
Knowing you.
都是我的錯
It was my fault.
我他媽親手造成的
I fucking did this.
我只想抱著她 看看她
And all I wanna do is grab her and see her
告訴她我很抱歉 可我卻做不了
and tell her that I'm sorry, and I can't.
她走了
She's gone.
寶貝 你能大點聲嗎
Sweetheart, can you speak up?
你用這麼可悲的雞兒聲說話
It's a little hard to hear you
我可聽不太清
with that pity dick in your mouth.
聽我說 小可憐 你得活下去
Now, look, sugar. You need to just keep living.
謝謝你...
Thank you...
馬修·麥康納 你的話真是金玉良言
Matthew McConaughey, your words are a treasure.
要聆聽痛苦
Listen to the pain.
它既是歷史老師 也是占蔔師
It's both history teacher and fortune teller.
痛苦教會我們認清自己 韋德
Pain teaches us who we are, Wade.
有時這很難熬 我們會覺得自己就要死了
Sometimes, it's so bad, we feel like we're dying.
但不曾觸摸過死亡 也就不算真正活過 不是嗎
But we can't really live till we've died a little, can we?
韋德
Wade?
- 韋德 - 我在這呢 艾爾西
- Wade? - I'm right here, Althea.
這大概是我聽過
And that is the most beautiful thing
最美妙的話了
I've ever heard.
你真是太對了
You're absolutely right.
我要去干點兒壞事了
I'm about to do something terrible.
到這 都連上了
There. All caught up.
不曾觸摸過死亡 就不算真正活過
You can't really live until you've died a little.
我們來檢驗一下這個理論吧
Let's test that theory, shall we?
產子計劃正式啟動
Baby factory's open for business.
咱倆是"瘋"味相投
Your crazy matches my crazy.
我永遠也不會給孩子起名為托德的
I will never, ever let our child be named Todd.
滑雪球游戲幣
Skee-Ball token.
國際婦女節快樂
Happy International Women's Day.
聽我說 我最近一直在想
Listen, I've been thinking a lot.
真的？
Really?
想的是為什麼我們倆這麼合拍
About why we're so good together.
我愛你 韋德·威爾遜
I love you, Wade Wilson.
內莎
Ness?
Ness.
內莎 這裡有東西擋著 我過不去
Ness, there's something here. I can't get to you.
你的心不在正確的位置
Your heart's not in the right place.
等等 你說什麼
Wait, hold on. What?
你的心不在正確的位置
Your heart's not in the right place.
等下 你說我的心
Wait. What do you mean
不在正確的位置是什麼意思？ 到底什麼意思...
my heart's not in the right place? What does it...
對你的不幸我深感抱歉 韋德
I'm terribly sorry for your loss, Wade.
你已經碎成渣了
You're broken.
我的天哪 我認得那個聲音
Oh, God. I know that voice.
心在正確的位置
"Heart's in the right place."
心不在正確的位置 那是什麼意思
"Heart's in the right..." What does that mean?
你已經睡了三天了
You've been sleep for three days.
我替你穿的衣服
I took the liberty of dressing you.
不是吧
No shit.
我他媽怎麼就不能死
Why can't I fucking die?
摘下你的面具 韋德
Take your mask off, Wade.
我們得談談
We must talk.
你需要重新開始
You need fresh start.
經過訓練 你可以成為X戰警的一員
With training, you can be X-Man.
你在浪費你的時間 閃瞎眼的耶穌先生
You're wasting your time, Shiny Jesus.
我不是當X戰警的料
I'm not X-Man material.
年度最謙虛獎得主
Understatement of the year.
韋德 這是雪緒
Wade, Yukio.
雪緒 這是韋德
Yukio, Wade.
我滴個中指啊 這又是個啥
What in the fuck knuckles is this?
這是我女朋友 你個思維狹隘的蠢貨
She's my girlfriend, you intolerant shit.
哇 先別急著開炮 "福克斯和朋友們"
Whoa! Pump the hate brakes, Fox & Friends.
我只是驚訝竟然有人會跟你約會
I'm just surprised anyone would date you.
居然還是小馬寶莉裡的碧琪
Especially Pinkie Pie from My Little Pony.
我喜歡這家伙
I like this guy.
他早晚會惡心到你
Give him a chance.
看到你這幅德行真開心
It's great seeing you like this.
是啊
Yeah.
再見 韋德
Bye, Wade!
到了我們這兒就要按我們的規矩來
Now, some ground rules while under our roof.
第一條 不可殺人
"Rule number one. No killing...
任何人 永遠都不行 不管是多壞的人
"anyone ever, no matter how bad.
第二條 把冰箱裡自己的東西做好標...
"Rule two. Label everything in refrigerator."
韋德
Wade?
Wade!
不要追我
Don't try to chase me.
我還沒准備好被人碰到呢
I'm not ready to be touched again.
看牆上有好多白人老頭
All these elderly white men on the walls...
真該帶我的防流氓哨來
Should have brought my rape whistle.
那些在掉下來之後就已經壞掉了哦
Those were already damaged after they fell there!
話說我在這兒到底要做什麼
What am I supposed to do around here, anyway?
坐成一圈傾吐心聲嗎
Sit in a share circle, talk about my feelings?
還有我到底要怎麼坐成一圈啊
And how would I do that exactly?
這的人都他媽死哪去了？
'Cause where the fuck is everyone?
總是只有你和負音波少年彈頭
It's always just you
最長的名字沒有之一
and Negasonic Teenage Longest Name Ever...
夠了
Enough!
我說了不要碰我
I said no touching!
你他媽 操
What the fuck?
還以為電影公司會對我們好一點
You'd think the studio would throw us a bone.
他們就不能重新起用哪個著名的X戰警嗎
They can't just dust off one of the famous X-Men?
長著巨大鴿子翅膀的那貨怎麼樣
How 'bout that putz with the giant pigeon wings?
那些人在那干嘛呢
What do those do anyway, huh?
讓他們離地三尺
Carry him three feet off the ground
然後去爭搶最近的松餅屑嗎
to snatch up the nearest muffin crumb?
不不不
No, no, no!
我完全不是當X戰警的料
I am not X-Man material at all.
首先...
First off...
我甚至都不是處男了 其次...
I'm not even a virgin. Second and more...
在我看你自哀自怨的時候
I should have left you
就不該想著拉你一把
in the self-pitying mess I found you in.
但是這就是朋友該做的 他們會出現
But this is what friends do. They show up!
不是在你一切順利的時候
Not when convenient or easy.
而是在你有麻煩的時候 而你非常擅長制造麻煩
When hard, and you always make it hard.
你現在情況差極了
You are unwell.
我為了救你可以兩肋插刀
I'm sticking my neck out bringing you here.
其中一個殺死
Wait. One of the assholes
瓦內莎的混蛋跑了
who killed Vanessa got away.
我的天吶
Oh, Jesus Christ!
韋德 不管他們是誰
Wade, whoever they are...
我們會找到他們 再讓他們接受正義的制裁
we track them down and bring them to justice.
是我
It was me.
我就是那個逃跑的混蛋
I'm the asshole who got away.
我把他們都殺死了 除了我自己
I killed every last one of them, except me.
我殺死不了自己
Couldn't kill me.
我們本來要建立一個家庭的
We were gonna start a family.
我們本來...
We were, uh...
我們本來要成為一家人了
We were gonna be a family.
韋德
Wade...
瓦內莎已經去世了 她不會死而復生
Vanessa is gone. She's not coming back.
這兒也許不是你想要的那個家庭
This may not be family you want...
但是你會需要我們這個家庭的
but it's family you need.
你本心地善良
You have a good heart.
它屬於這裡 在它可以成長的地方
It belongs here where it can grow.
你剛剛說什麼？
What did you say?
我的心怎麼了？
About my heart?
我覺得我的心到正確的位置了
I think I'm in the right place.
韋德
Wade.
韋德！
Wade!
嘿 我在玩X教授的腦波強化機呢
Hey, I was just taking Cerebro for a spin here...
看看未來長什麼樣
looking deep into the future.
這玩意...
Phew. This thing...
- 腦波強化機不是這麼用的 - 腦波強化機不是這麼用的
- That's not how Cerebro works. - That's not how Cerebro works.
是的 就是這麼用的
Yes. Yes, it is.
- 我們有任務了 - 我們有任務了
- We have mission. - We have mission.
我們有任務了 但是你們去
We do. You do.
你們在外出任務注意安全
You guys be safe out there.
- 不 我想讓你和我們一起 - 不 你想讓我和你們一起
- No, I want you to join. - No, you want me to join.
不好意思 你說什麼？
I'm sorry, what?
你已經准備好了
You are ready.
這是個很爛的主意 而且是不會有好結果的
That's a terrible idea, and it's gonna end badly.
你想知道我是怎麼知道的嗎？ 我來給你個提示
You wanna know how I know? I'll give you a hint.
它在我的腦袋上
It's on my head
而且聞起來像帕特裡克·斯圖爾特
and smells like Patrick Stewart.
五分鐘後X戰機上集合
Be at the X-Jet in five.
WHIT電視台 艾琳·梅利韋瑟為你報道
Irene Merryweather, WHIT News.
為您播報埃塞克斯之家變種人治療所
Live here at a breaking news situation
發生的突發狀況
at the Essex House for Mutant Rehabilitation.
一個變種人男孩似乎
A mutant boy is appearing to have
與我背後的這些警察
some sort of an incident...
- 發生了衝突 - 離我遠點
- with police here behind me. - Get away from me!
有兩輛警車已被掀翻
There are two police vehicles that are overturned.
- 現場發生交火 - 滾開 退後
- There are open fires. - Fuck off! Stay back!
現場一片狼藉
A scene of absolute chaos here.
冷靜
Calm down.
我會燒死你的 不要靠近我
I'll burn you! You stay back!
離我遠點
Get away from me!
你想死嗎
You wanna fucking die?
這麼看來 X戰警就快來了...
And it appears as if the X-Men are arriving...
散開
Scatter!
帶了一個實習戰警過來
...with what appears to be a trainee.
大家都冷靜一下 專業的到了
Everyone, calm down! The pros are here. I...
我們是X戰警
We're the X-Men!
一個用來隱喻60年代種族主義的現代詞
A dated metaphor for racism in the '60s.
來吧 尊重和..
So, respect.
稍息吧 警官們
At ease, Officer.
你在搞什麼？
What are you doing?
我的工作啊
My job!
是你說我已經准備好了
You're the one who said I was ready,
而我已經明確說我還沒准備好
and I frankly disagreed with you.
但我們還是來到了這裡 試圖解決彼此之間的分歧
But here we are, trying to overcome our differences.
就想碧昂絲說的 拜托了
Like Beyonce says, "Please...
拜托你別再出軌了
"Please, stop cheating on me."
喂
Hey!
這是第五起意外了
This is the fifth incident.
這孩子應該關到冰盒監獄裡 而不是在這
This kid needs to be in the Ice Box, not here.
羅素需要我們的救護
Russell belongs in our care.
不應該待在監獄裡 我向你保證
Not in prison. I assure you...
一切情況盡在我們的掌握之中
we have everything under control.
退後 我會燒死你的
Stay back! I'll burn you!
並不覺得一切
Not getting a real
盡在你們掌控啊 馬蒂
"under control" vibe here, Marty.
- 他叫格倫 對吧 - 是丹尼爾
- It is Glen, isn't it? - Daniel.
我才是提問的那個 讓我跟那孩子聊聊
I'll ask the questions. Let me talk to the kid.
你就跟你奇怪又神秘的...性感小嘴唇待在這兒吧
You stay here with your weird, secret sex lips.
你想死嗎
You wanna die?
他真可愛
This kid's adorable.
真不知道我為什麼裝了一排空尖彈
I don't know why I packed the hollow points.
我能把你燒得不能自理
I'll burn your balls off!
第一天干活 我好緊張哦
First day. I'm so nervous!
你剛剛是說空尖彈了嗎？
Did you just say "hollow points"?
對啊 應該
Yeah, probably should've
帶個超級水槍來的
brought a Super Soaker.
嘿 小伙計
Hi, there!
退後 不然我就讓賈斯汀·比伯死翹翹
Stay back or Justin Bieber dies!
賈斯汀·比伯 他說你是賈斯汀·比伯
Justin Bieber. He called you Justin Bieber.
等等 不管你有什麼大招...
Hold on! Wait, wait, wait!
別著急用 好吧
Okay, let's not do whatever that is.
我們來聊聊天吧
Okay? Let's just talk!
你叫羅素 是嗎
It's Russell, right?
- 火拳 - 火拳啊
- Firefist. - Firefist.
這可真是個好名字啊 火是從哪兒開始燒的啊？
Ooh, that's a great name. Where does it burn?
只是拳頭還是整個手肘都行
Just the fist, or all the way up to the elbow?
絕對是整個手肘都行
Definitely all the way up to the elbow.
悄悄的給我過來 不然會有麻煩的
Come quietly, or there will be trouble.
- 你居然偷《機械戰警》的台詞 - 《機械戰警》
- You stole that from Robocop! - That's from Robocop!
你還是別說話了
Just stand down!
真給我丟人 聽著
You're embarrassing me. Look, Fire...
我說不出來啊哈哈哈 實在是對不起哈哈哈哈哈
Oh, my God! I can't say it! I'm so sorry!
啊操  你他媽超出我的底線了
Oh, shit! That fucking does it!
手放在膝蓋後面
Put your hands behind your knees
頭朝下 立刻馬上
and get down on your head! Now!
韋德 第一條規定是什麼
Wade! What was first rule?
把冰箱裡所有東西都貼上標簽
Label everything in the refrigerator!
- 不要把衝突升級 - 規定就是用來打破的
- Do not escalate! - Rules are meant to be broken!
完全不是
That's the exact opposite
這個意思
of what they're meant for!
操  行吧
Fuck! Fine!
我從頭再來一遍
I'll start from the beginning.
- 我的名字是死侍 我是X戰警
My name is Deadpool, and I'm an X-Man.
- 實習戰警 - 閉嘴
- Trainee! - Shut it!
行了 我知道了
Look, I get it.
好嗎 你很害怕
All right, you're scared.
孤身一人
Alone.
你沒有家人
You got no family.
我也沒有家人
I didn't have a family, either.
你住在這個垃圾堆 猜猜怎麼著
You live in this dump. Guess what?
我以前就住在一個和這個一模一樣的破地方
I used to live in a shithole just like it.
但是你知道嗎 現在你的情況更糟
But you know something? To make matters worse...
因為現在是你人生中一段很迷茫的時間
it's a confusing time in your life right now.
你的身體正發生著一些劇烈的變化
Your body is going through some fiery changes.
跑偏了 我跑太偏了
Too far? I went too far, didn't I?
這招挺過癮啊
That was effervescent.
要待在學校 小屁孩
Stay in school, kid.
或者不待 我就沒待
Or don't. I didn't.
我是一名X戰警
And I'm an X-Man.
實習戰警
Trainee.
靠
Fuck it!
超級英雄版著陸要來了
Superhero landing coming up!
操 操 操
Ah, fuck, fuck, fuck!
這招太不實用了
That is so not practical.
我覺得這X戰警的排場還真挺不錯
I could get used to this X-Man shit.
實習戰警
Trainee!
實習戰警也行
給他戴上項圈 控制住他 快
Get a power restraint on him. Now!
噴水槍們 別著急 都結束了 我們抓到你了
Calm down, squirt. It's over. We got ya.
這是干嘛的
What's that do?
力量抑制項圈
Power-dampening collar.
能隔絕所有變種能力
Shuts down all mutant abilities.
無法掙脫 除非你用手榴彈炸
You can't get it off. Unless you've got a grenade.
剛開始讓哥用這個不就沒這麼多事了
Huh. Could've used one of those in the first act.
謝謝你
Thank you!
真是太令人激動了
That was absolutely thrilling.
這是真正的英雄主義
True heroism in action.
我們欠你個人情
We are in your debt.
接下來就由我們接手吧
We can take it from here.
求求你 把我送到冰盒監獄裡吧
Take me to the Ice Box, please!
去哪裡都比這兒好
Anywhere's better than here.
相信我 孩子
Believe me, son,
你不會想進冰盒監獄的
you do not wanna go to the Ice Box.
進去吧 年輕人
Let's get you inside, young man.
不 等等 等等
No, wait, wait. Wait.
你們就 你們就站那兒別過來
You guys stay there.
這些家伙傷害你嗎
Those guys hurt you?
誰
Who?
老禿頭  賈裡德·庫什納
Baldilocks? Jared Kushner?
還是兩個一起
Both of 'em?
去他媽的
Oh, fuck it.
四到五個時刻
Four or five moments!
你說啥
I'm sorry?
四 五個瞬間
Four or five moments!
成為英雄只需要這幾個瞬間
That's all it takes to be a hero.
人們都認為你用英雄的方式起床
People think you wake up a hero...
用英雄的方式刷牙
brush your teeth a hero...
用英雄的方式擼到洗手液瓶裡
ejaculate into a soap dispenser a hero.
但其實不是 變成一個英雄
But, no, being a hero takes only a few moments!
只需要幾分鐘
A few moments...
用幾分鐘的時間去做一些沒人會用的肮髒手段
doing the ugly stuff no one else will do.
住手
No!
退後 別開火
Stand down! Hold your fire!
- 韋德 你都干了些什麼- 鋼力士 不
- Wade, what did you do? - Colossus, no!
這孩子遭到虐待了 你能看出來
That kid was abused! You can tell.
-  你一直都能看出來 - 我們是有規矩的
- You can always tell! - We have rules!
你不是法官 陪審團 也不是行刑官
You are not judge, jury or executioner!
去你媽的規矩 我只為正確的事而戰
Fuck your rules! I fight for what's right!
那麼有些時候 你就必須不擇手段
And sometimes you gotta fight dirty!
這是你最後一次讓我失望了 韋德
You let me down for the last time, Wade.
把他們關進去
Okay, get these guys in the pod.
把他們送到冰盒監獄
Take them to the Ice Box.
你好啊 小寶貝
Hey, baby!
我很好奇我會進什麼幫
I wonder what gang I'll be in.
- 會有《哈利·波特》裡那種分級的帽子嗎？ - 你好
- Is there, like, a Sorting Hat? - Hi.
走快一點
Go!
最左邊 傻X
Hard left, douchebag.
來吧 你先進
Please, after you.
街上又少了一個惡心的變種人
Another disgusting mutant off the streets.
願上帝保佑美國
God bless America.
我們去吃薄餅吧
Let's get a taco.
晚安了 你個煩人的渾球
Nighty-night, you annoying prick!
但我要告訴你最大的謊話是什麼
I'mma tell you what the big lie is.
廁紙
Toilet paper.
廁紙是公認好用的日用品
Toilet paper is a plenty fine appetizer.
但然後...
But, then...
好奇牌紙尿褲是天然護理濕巾
Huggies Natural Care wet wipes.
那才是你該用的
That's your main course.
他們又軟又濕潤 他們是為嬰兒設計的
They're soft, they're moist. They're for babies.
最後 再來一張廁紙
Finally, one more pass with the toilet paper,
幫忙清除多余的水分
maybe clear out that excess moisture.
如果你能找到一個吹風機
Maybe treat yourself to a blow and go,
也許還會讓自己隨用隨走
if you can get you a hair dryer.
只要30秒就可以讓你...
Just about 30 seconds will do you good.
什麼鬼
The fuck?
幾幾年了
Year?
啥
What?
今年是哪一年
What year is it?
你這問的是什麼傻X問題
What kind of dumbass question is that to ask?
你不要想拿回你的超能力了
You're a long way from your superpowers.
是啊
Yeah.
操
Fuck!
我想當一個超級英雄
I wanted to be a superhero.
我一直想要一件自己的超級裝備
Always wanted a real super suit.
發生了什麼事
What happened?
你什麼時候見過加大碼的超級英雄
When was the last time you saw a plus-sized superhero?
從沒見過
Never.
這個社會歧視胖子
The industry discriminates.
去他媽的超級英雄
Fuck superheroes.
去他媽的所有人
Fuck everyone.
我離開這裡之後的要做的第一件事
The first thing I wanna do when I get out of here...
就是活活燒死校長
burn the headmaster alive...
然後跟他燒焦的屍體來張自拍
and then take a selfie with his smoldering corpse.
誰說監獄裡學不到東西
Who says prison isn't reformative?
那混蛋最討厭變種人
Fucker hates mutants.
被我治愈的怪胎
Blessed are the wicked
都是上帝賜福
who are healed by my hand.
你們的能力
Your abilities.
我知道他們有多誘人
I know how seductive they are.
拜托 別再哭泣
Now, please don't cry.
明天 我會找到這裡塊頭最大的家伙
Tomorrow, we'll find the biggest guy in here...
我要讓他成為我...
and we'll make him our...
那是什麼
What was that?
那就是這裡最大的家伙
That is the biggest guy in here.
告訴你個冰盒監獄監獄的小趣聞
Fun fact about the Ice Box...
雖然沒人見過
though no one's ever seen it,
不過他們的地下室裡關了一個怪物
they keep a monster in the basement.
就在這一坨
Right next to a huge,
新鮮出爐的伏筆附近
steaming bowl of foreshadowing.
聽著
Look.
我保護不了你
I can't protect you.
戴著這個項圈
With this collar on,
我的超能力就是不受控制的的癌症
my superpower is just unbridled cancer.
給我一份弓和箭 我就只能當個鷹眼
Give me a bow and arrow, I'm basically Hawkeye.
現在如果你沒事了
Now, if you'll excuse me...
我就努力長腫瘤 等著去天堂見瓦內莎了
I've got tumors to grow. Vanessa awaits.
我得先給我們做一把短刀
I'll start by making us a shank.
- 你是真聽話啊 - 我偷了那個衛兵的筆
- Good listening. - I stole that guard's pen...
指的是菊花裡
然後把他藏在了古老的監獄錢包裡
and stashed it in the old prison wallet,
你懂我的意思吧？
if you know what I'm saying.
監獄錢包
Prison wallet?
我真希望我不知道你在說什麼
I really hope I don't know what you're saying.
我能聽到你在裡面掏東西的聲音
I can hear you rummaging around in there.
現在更新一下
And to update you
之前報道的一則消息
on the story reported earlier,
經過了在埃塞克斯之家變種人治療所外
after a lengthy standoff
漫長的僵持階段
outside the Essex House for Mutant Rehabilitation...
兩名變種人遭到逮捕
two mutants were arrested
並被轉移到冰盒監獄監獄
and transported to the Ice Box...
進入修復模式
Entering repair mode.
...數輛警車被毀
...several police cars were destroyed
警方聯系到X戰警們來到現場恢復秩序
and the X-Men were called in to restore order.
七號和九號牢房
Cells seven and nine
現禁止醫療人員進入
now off-limits for medical personnel.
七號和九號牢房
Cells seven and nine
現禁止醫療人員進入
now off-limits for medical personnel.
別 別這麼做
Don't do that.
啥 你為什麼要對我拋媚眼
What? Why are you winking at me?
我會罩你的
I got your back.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
我說過我會保護你
You're sick, I gotta protect you.
可離我遠點吧 小屁孩
Just leave me alone, kid.
真他媽好
Oh, great.
喲 看看我們的新朋友
Well, hello there, new fish.
能在這兒看到一些新面孔真令人開心
It's nice to see some fresh faces around here.
這只是一小部分
I've done some light catalog work...
不過說真的 做模特只是成為演員的一個小台階
but, really, modeling is just a stepping stone to acting.
我在和他說話
- I was talking to him. - Oh.
我們之前見過嘛 我不記得這個胡子啊
Have we met? I can't place your mustache.
- 布萊克(黑人)·湯姆·卡西迪  - 白人 韋德·威爾遜
- Black Tom Cassidy. - White Wade Wilson.
你丫超能力是什麼 文化挪用嗎
What's your superpower? Cultural appropriation?
你應該是這裡最能打的小騷貨
You're supposed to be the toughest cunt in here.
但我看你一點都不像
You don't look like much to me.
監獄第一法則 小白臉
First rule of the yard, fuckface...
找到勢力最大的家伙 並讓他成為你的
find the biggest guy and make him your...
第二大的家伙
Second biggest guy.
我最不需要的就是肝炎了
The last thing I need is more hepatitis.
居然還很滑 這張桌子需要好好擦一下
Oh, it's slippery, too. This table needs a wipe down!
有人來擦一下這張桌子嗎
Can we get a wipe down on the table?
小屁孩 我認為你站錯隊了
Kid, I think you picked the wrong side.
不 我沒有 他是我朋友
No, I didn't! He's my friend!
閉嘴 我們不是朋友
Zip it. We're not friends.
你馬上會被小丁丁抽臉...
You're about to get dick-slapped.
我玩得真他媽開心 你當時各種被打...
I had so much fun! You were like...
當時我說："坐下 你個傻吊"
And I was like, "Take a seat, shit dick."
求你了 讓我安靜地去死吧
Just let me die in peace.
我們強強聯手超棒的
We make a great team!
我們不是一伙人
Oh, God! We're not a team.
你剛才在那說什麼？我們是朋友 搭檔
Why'd you say that back there? We're friends, partners.
我們不是搭檔 也不是朋友
We're not partners or friends.
這故事不會以我倆開車駛向夕陽作為結尾的
This doesn't end with us riding into the sunset.
它會以我死於癌症結束
It ends with me dying of cancer...
而你會奪得冰盒監獄最軟嘴巴獎
and you winning the Ice Box award for softest mouth.
在這個世界上我關心的人只有一個
There's only one person in this world
不過她已經死了
that I care about, and she's gone.
你想要活下去嗎
You wanna survive?
不要試圖去挑釁勢力最大的人
Stop trying to shank the biggest guys in here...
要去和他們做朋友
and make friends with them.
找一個人做朋友
Make friends with someone.
除了我 任何人都行
Anyone but me.
甚至布萊克·提姆也行
Maybe even Black Tim.
還是布萊克·埃文 我忘了他叫什麼了
Black Evan, I don't know.
我只記得他是非裔美國人
All I remember is he was African-American.
系統故障
System malfunctioning.
7 12 14 27號牢房
Cells 7, 12, 14, 27.
滾回你們的牢房 你們這群變種雜碎 快滾進去
Back in your cells, you filthy mutants! Get in there!
1 3 7 8號牢房
Cells 1, 3, 7, 8.
搜尋中
Searching.
牢房0-4 已鎖定
Cell 04 located.
門打不開
Door won't open!
他媽的跪下
On your fucking knees!
那裡是我們的牢房
That was our cell.
這老混蛋脾氣這麼爆
What did I do to piss off a grumpy old fucker
還裝備冬兵手臂 我什麼時候惹到他的？
with a Winter Soldier arm?
離我遠點 孩子
Get away from me, kid!
聽我的 快走
Listen to me! Go!
你好啊 羅素
Hello, Russell.
你好啊 超能力
Hello, superpowers.
你到底是誰
Who are you?
我是蝙蝠俠
I'm Batman.
這槍真帶勁兒
Oh. That's got some zip.
別想了 連我都殺不了我自己
Don't feel bad. Even I can't kill me.
說
Talk!
到底是怎樣的一個無恥混蛋
What kind of spineless shit stick
才會去殺一個14歲的孩子
tries to kill a 14-year-old boy?
你最好立刻交代
You might wanna start talking!
因為我有很多次這樣開火的經歷
'Cause I got a long history of firing at times like this!
名字是電鎖
The name's Cable.
我來自未來 不要多管閑事
I'm from the future. Just walk away.
所以你來自未來 行吧
So, you're from the future.
那我問你三個問題
I have three questions then.
第一 重音回響還流行嗎
One, is dubstep still a thing?
第二 《鯊卷風》出到第幾部了
Two, which Sharknado are we on?
第三 到了什麼時候觀眾才會說
And three, at what point do audiences say...
"真是看夠了機械手臂了"
"Enough with the robotic arms"?
只有娘炮才玩重音回響
Dubstep's for pussies.
你好黑暗啊
You're so dark!
你確定你不是DC宇宙來的嗎
Are you sure you're not from the DC universe?
我超愛重音回響
I love dubstep!
那是個芬妮包嗎
Is that a fanny pack?
我在1990年幾乎沒有過一個一模一樣的
I used to have one of those in 1990-never.
留個紀念吧
Something to remember you by.
把那個還給我 我在哪它就在哪
Give me that back! That goes with me everywhere.
就像你那個惡心的芬妮包的回憶一樣
Like the memory of your fucking fanny pack!
你為什麼要保護那個孩子
Why are you protecting the kid?
我一點都不在乎他
I don't give a fuck about him...
他可能有戀母情結
and his Are You My Mother? complex!
這個是干什麼的
What's this one do?
在每部電影裡
In every film, there's a moment
都有主人公跌入谷底的時候
when the hero hits rock bottom.
在《冰上輕馳》裡 約翰·坎迪珍愛的雪橇
In Cool Runnings, it was when John Candy's
壞了的時候
prized bobsled broke.
在《人體蜈蚣》裡 是那些人
In Human Centipede, it was when those people...
簽了要拍那部電影的時候
signed on to be in that movie.
但是在這部電影裡 這個嘛...
But in this film, well...
我的谷底就是現在你們看的這段了
you're looking at it.
他媽的跪下 變種人
On your fucking knees, mutant.
跌到
Rock...
谷底了
meet bottom.
我愛你 韋德·威爾遜
I love you, Wade Wilson.
內莎
Ness?
嘿 內莎
Hey, Ness!
妮莎 能讓我進去嗎？
Ness, can you let me in?
求你了
Please! Please.
我的天啊
Jesus.
你給我指的路我看不清啊
You're not giving me a lot of direction here.
我已經走投無路了
I'm at the end of my rope.
我加入了X戰警
Then I joined the X-Men.
我進監獄了
I went to prison. I, uh...
我的心該放在那個孩子身上嗎？
Is it the kid?
孩子們給我們機會讓我們變得比以前更好
Kids give us a chance to be better than we used to be.
是那個孩子
The kid!
瓦妮莎的意思是讓我把心放在那孩子身上
That's exactly what she meant.
你的心不在正確的位置
Your heart needs to be in the right place.
我絕對不會丟下那個孩子
I'm not gonna abandon this kid.
從來都沒有人幫助過他 從來沒有
He's never had anyone, ever.
我得無私一點
I need to be selfless.
好吧 可是 但這話是什麼意思
Yeah, but what does that mean?
這句話的意思是 我要去救羅素
It means I'm gonna save Russell.
也許我救不了瓦妮莎...
Maybe I couldn't save Vanessa...
但也許我還能救一個新西蘭的超大碼少年
but maybe I can save a robust teenager from New Zealand.
好吧 我說的是無私這個詞
Yeah, but what I mean is, like, the world "selfless."
我其實不知道這詞什麼意思
I literally don't know what that means.
我的天
Jesus Christ.
聽著 我的人說
Okay, look. According to my guy, okay...
那些變種人
those muties are being transferred
要被送到一個80裡外的控制區
to a supermax, 80 miles away.
好 我會半路攔下他們
Great, I'll pick 'em off along the way.
先別急著激動好嗎 哥們
Hold your testicles there, buddy, okay?
我們說的是一只全副武裝的運送隊
We're talking about an armored convoy...
還有個來自未來的超級大壞兵
and a vicious super soldier from the future...
正等著把你的腦袋變成一個可操型煙灰缸
that is looking to turn your skull into a fuckable ashtray.
你知道我們需要什麼嗎
You know what we need to do?
我們需要一個無敵戰隊
We need to build a fucking team.
他們要能打 不死守道德規範
We need 'em tough, morally flexible...
足夠年輕
and young enough so they can carry
至少10到12年內不會散伙
this franchise 10 to 12 years.
我的身體就是死亡機器
My body is an instrument of death.
現在不行 多芬德
Not now, Dopinder.
我能幫上大忙的
I could be of great use.
你的超能力是什麼
What's your superpower?
- 勇氣 - 真是太可愛了
- Courage. - That's adorable.
那你有勇氣去看看自動販售機裡
Do you have the courage to check and see...
還有沒有足夠的衛生棉嗎
if there are enough sanitary napkins in the dispenser?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
真抱歉讓你看到這個
I'm sorry you had to see that,
哦不 我很高興你聽見了
although I'm glad you heard it.
好了 我去招人收簡歷
All right, I'll put out a call for resumes.
但是我們可不包醫保和牙保
But we're not paying medical or dental.
我去領英網上看看
It's time to get back on LinkedIn.
本次轉移將在8點開始
Transport will begin at 0800 hours...
你他媽要干啥
What the fuck do you want?
那他媽是我的布丁
That's my fucking pudding.
- 去你的布丁 - 你喜歡布丁?
- Fuck your pudding! - You like pudding?
有人嗎
Hello?
我知道你在裡面
I know you're in there.
在這裡做老大一定不輕松吧
Must be hard being the biggest guy in here.
獨霸山巔
Lonely at the top, eh?
他們明天就會轉移我們
They're moving us tomorrow.
也許到時我可以救你出來
Maybe I can get you out of here.
我們可以把整個世界都操翻
And we can make the whole world our bitch.
我們需要一個暗號
We need a secret code.
不行 這個太蠢了 羅素 你個大傻瓜
No, that's stupid, Russell. Idiot.
我們是一伙的了
We're a team.
我們就像匪幫 就像黑社會
We're like thugs, we're like gangsters.
歌曲《real thug》裡的兩位重量級匪幫說唱成員
我就像2Pac 你就是Ice Cube
I'm like Tupac, and you're like Ice Cube.
似乎她還會說唱
Supposedly, she can rap, too.
我喜歡喲
I like that.
棒極了 這些都棒極了
Terrific, these are all terrific.
見一見喧囂
Meet Bedlam.
名字很帥啊 超能力呢
Cool name! Superpowers?
我可以扭曲
I can distort
電磁場
electrical fields.
包括你腦子裡的磁場
Including the one inside your brain...
可以讓你焦慮 疑惑
causing anxiety, confusion...
和痛苦
pain.
所以基本上 你就是戴夫•馬修斯
So, basically, you're Dave Matthews.
我們用得著他
We can use him.
我是扎格斯特
I'm Zeitgeist.
不錯 我喜歡
Cool. I like it.
我猜你能把手指放在 呃
So you have the power
社會的脈搏上
to put your finger on the pulse of society?
不
No.
不是的 我能吐出強酸的嘔吐物
No, I spit acidic vomit.
- 哦 - 要不要我吐一下
- Oh. - Do you want me
- 給你們看看 - 不不不用了
- to demonstrate? - No!
我們信你
We'll take your word for it.
謝謝 我跟你講 我們都去阿比斯餐廳吃過飯 懂了吧？
Thank you. Yeah. Listen, we've all eaten at Arby's, okay?
這位 就是隱形人
And this is the Vanisher.
可是
But...
隱形人
Vanisher!
厲害啊  對吧
Nice! Right?
他不在這兒 對吧
He's not here, is he?
他可能是遲到了
He may be running late.
我的名字是鏽蝕但你們可以叫我碎星
My name's Rusty, but I go by Shatterstar.
不錯 對
That's good, yeah.
- 鏽蝕就…很糟糕 - 是啊
- "Rusty" is terrible. - Toughie.
- 那麼 你是哪兒來的   - 一個叫莫傑世界的星球
- So, uh, where are you from? - The planet Mojo World.
- 所以你是個外星人…吧 - 這名字取得不好
- So you're an alien, I guess. - Bad name.
外星人對我們有什麼好處
How does that, uh, help us?
基本上說 我每一點都比你們強
I'm basically better than you at everything.
那麼一瞬間 我希望找這麼個星球
Just once, I'm gonna find a planet of people
上面全是什麼都比我差的飯桶
that are worse than me at everything.
一大群實用的傻蛋
A whole bunch of functional idiots.
我一定要去那當他們的超人
I'm gonna go there, and I'm gonna be their Superman.
那不就是加拿大嗎？
Isn't that Canada?
你把你滿嘴噴糞的的臭嘴給我閉上
You shut your goddamn trash mouth!
- 這是 - 多米諾
- Meet... - Domino.
- 你有什麼絕活  - 我運氣好
- What's your shtick? - I'm lucky.
如果你運氣那麼好 那你為啥會出現在這兒
If you're so lucky, then what are you doing here with us?
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
- 她這話是什麼意思
What's that supposed to mean?
就是我還不知道的意思
It means that I don't know yet.
不過我來這是有原因的
But there's a reason why I'm here,
不過到時候我就能知道了
and I'll know when I know.
一般我的事都會迎刃而解
Everything usually works out for me.
幸運不是一種超能力
Luck isn't a superpower.
- 不對 它是 -不 它不是
- Yes, it is. - No, it isn't.
- 是的 它是 - 不是的 女士
- Yes, it is. - No, ma'am.
馬裡奧·"不是"佩茲
- Mmm-hmm. - Mario No-pez.
- 是的  - 奶酪薄餅
- Yeah. - Nacho cheese.
不不不 絕對是...
No, it definitely is. I really...
絕對不可能...
There's no way that it...
對不起 我剛才打斷了你
Sorry, I was interrupting you.
- 抱歉 不是 是我打斷了你 - 不 不 你先來吧
- Sorry. No, I interrupted you. - No, no, no. You can go first.
我剛才准備說 不 它不是
Oh, I was just gonna say, "No, it isn't."
而我是想把話題帶會到 是的 它是
I was gonna just bring it back to that yes, it is.
讓我們各退一步然後說 不 它不是
Let's meet in the middle and say, "No, it isn't."
- 但是它的確實是 - 好吧...
- But it is. - Okay.
- 你被錄用了 - 你被錄用了
- You're hired! - You're hired.
哦 我真幸運
Oh, lucky me.
她真有趣
She's great.
來吧 最後一個
And last, but not least...
彼得
Peter.
你這個是照騙嗎 還是...
Am I getting catfished here or...?
你有什麼超能力想給我們展示麼？
Any powers you wanna tell us about?
沒有嗎
No.
我沒有超能力
I don't have one.
我就是看到了廣告 覺得...挺好玩的
Um, I just saw the ad and thought it looked fun.
- 你被錄用了
You're in.
- 耶 - 我操
- Yeah. - Fuck!
這工作真不錯
It's fulfilling work.
快走
Let's go!
這裡是押運車17號 正在離開冰盒監獄
This is Convoy 17 departing the Ice Box.
我們上路了
We are en route.
平靜的時光讓人松懈
Peacetime makes people soft.
我為戰爭而生
I was born into war.
戰爭養育了我
Bred into it.
好吧
Okay.
人們以為他們了解痛苦
People think they understand pain.
你經歷過最痛苦的感覺是什麼
What's the most pain you've ever felt?
這些繩子綁得很...
These restraints are pretty...
我已經列了個單子
I've got a list.
我會讓你體驗單子裡的各種痛苦
We're gonna work down it.
我們一起來完成
Together.
首先 我要掰彎一個東西
Number one, I'm gonna bend something.
一個不該被掰彎的東西
Something that was not meant to bend.
好 我要在這裡打斷你一下
I'm gonna stop you right there
因為 我不想讓你接著說了
because I'm not gonna make it to two.
我甚至連這一個都不想經歷
I won't even make it to one.
我很怕疼的 你知道嗎
I don't do well with pain, you know.
要是我磕到腳趾 那我今天什麼也別想干了
If I stub my toe, I'm done for the day.
他們把《大學生費莉希蒂》砍掉的時候 我就哭了
I cried when they canceled Felicity.
還有就是我非常害怕的時候 我會緊張地勃起
When I get really scared, I get nervous erections.
我現在就硬了
I have one right now.
別去看它 這樣只會讓它更糟
Don't look. It'll only make it worse.
我不想讓你傷害我
I don't want you to hurt me,
我會把一切都告訴你
and I'll tell you anything you wanna know.
除了他們在哪 我不能說
Except for where they are.
羅素在一輛沿著格裡·杜根大道
Russell's in a convoy heading southbound
向南行駛的押運車裡
on Gerry Duggan Parkway.
那個怪物和他一起 我要是你就是不會去招惹他
The monster's with them. I wouldn't fuck with him.
你清楚計劃的
You all know the plan.
攔截押運車
Intercept the convoy,
抓走男孩 但是動作要得體
grab the boy. But not inappropriately!
你知道嗎
You know what,
我也不會去惹死侍
I wouldn't fuck with Deadpool either.
因為他組了個隊 他是不可抵擋的
Because he's built a team. He's unstoppable.
他有只菊花筆 他會拿那玩意捅你的
He has an ass pen. He'll stab you with it.
當心這個家伙 電鎖
Watch out for this guy, Cable!
他非常矮 1米8左右 跟漫畫裡的設定不一樣
He's very short, 5'11". Not like in the comics.
如果我們成功了 我們就都能早點回家
And if we succeed, we all go home early.
如果你跟著他們 電鎖 我警告你
So if you go after them, Cable, I warn you...
這段時間有強風警報
there's a wind advisory in effect.
外面風好大啊
A little turbulent up here.
我不太知道這個叫電鎖的
I don't know much about this Cable fella...
但是我可以保證
but I guarantee he hasn't killed
他的殺人數跟黑素瘤比就差遠了
as many people as melanoma has.
我們越來越近了
We're getting close!
作為一個前X戰警...
As a former X-Man...
- 實習戰警 - 我謝你啊 喧囂
- Trainee. - Thank you, Bedlam.
他們如此露骨地使用帶有性別歧視意味的隊名
I was always appalled by the blatant sexism
讓我深感震驚
in the group's name.
"X-男"  男
X-Men! Men!
重點是我們的隊伍要有超前的思維
The point is, our group will be forward thinking.
性別中立
Gender neutral.
所以從現在開始 我們的隊名就是...
From now on, we'll be known as...
X特攻隊
X-Force.
這不會有點山寨嗎
Isn't that a little derivative?
我並沒有征求你的意見 彼得
I don't recall asking your opinion, Peter!
剛才那話不是我說的
That wasn't me.
飛機降到1300英尺時 我們就跳出去
Hang the laundry out at 1,300 feet...
截下押運車 救出男孩
intercept the convoy, and grab the boy.
我們開始屠殺吧 寶貝！
Let's bring on the carnage, baby!
看我表演吧
Get me on the ground, watch me go!
呼
Yeah!
已經忍不住要大殺特殺了
I can't wait to kill!
我只是想說我以這個隊為傲
I just wanna say how proud I am of this team.
你們知道嗎 你們看起來超級棒
You know, you guys look amazing!
隱形人 毫無疑問你的樣子也肯定棒極了
Vanisher, I have no doubt you look amazing too.
這就是
This is the family
我一直想擁有的大家庭 我有過...
that I've always dreamed of having and I...
媽的 我忘了
Ah, shit.
我有時會激動的說不出話來
I just get a little choked up sometimes.
我不想打斷你們 但是沒人
I hate to interrupt, but is anybody nervous
擔心這個強風嗎？
about the high winds?
- 蓋理 - 我叫彼得
- Gary. - My name's Peter.
我知道你是新來的 不過別緊張
I realize that you're new to this, but relax.
你是天選之子
You've been chosen by a higher power.
- 他剛是說自己是上帝嗎 - 他我覺得他是
- Did he just call himself God? - I think he did.
- 我想回家 - 我還想要
- I'd like to go home. - And I'd like...
麥當勞全年都賣烤汁豬排堡呢！
the McRib to be available year round,
但是有時願望是不會成真的
but sometimes dreams don't come true.
我在特種部隊呆了10年
I spent 10 years in Special Forces.
你覺得我們不跳出飛機
You think we didn't jump out of the plane
風就會小了嗎
because of a light breeze?
別說廢話了 小胡子
You're in this shit now, Mustache!
我吼你只是想震懾一下別人
I'm only yelling to impress the other guys.
我不會讓你有事的 甜甜熊
I'd never let anything happen to you, Sugarbear.
開始吧
Leonard, hit it!
衝！衝！衝！
Go! Go! Go!
玩的痛快吧！
Let's get some!
哦 太棒了
Oh, yeah!
押運車 十二點方向 聽我指揮
Convoy, 12 o'clock! On my command!
現在打開降落傘
Deploy! Oh, hey now!
有點偏離航線了
Little off course here.
我的個媽呀
Holy mommy fucking shit!
他們在這呢
Ah, there they are.
看看這群出色的小婊砸們
Look at these gorgeous sons of bitches.
真棒 這就對了 喧囂
Oh, yeah! That's right, Bedlam!
我操你奶奶的破村
No! Tripping motherfucking billies!
碎星 你沒問題的
Shatterstar. Okay, you got this.
左轉
Left!
左轉！
你個笨蛋 左轉啊！
No, stage left, you idiot!
至少我們發現
Well, I guess we found something
你不擅長什麼了
you're not better at.
隱形人
Vanisher.
也許風看不到你就不會刮到你
Maybe the wind can't blow what it can't see.
你認真的嗎
Oh! Really?
好吧 我們四個人也可以的
All right, we could do this with four.
甜甜熊 你可以的 哥們
Sugarbear. You got this, buddy!
這才對嘛 這才是X特攻隊的精神
That's the stuff! That's the X-Force spirit!
永遠不能低估有胡子的男人
Never underestimate a man with a mustache!
布魯克林的人都知道
Just ask anyone in Brooklyn.
我們成功了
We did it!
你真是個叼炸天的英雄
You're a goddamn superhero, you!
X特攻隊
X-Force!
X-Force.
彼得
Peter.
我抓住你了 伙計
I got you, buddy!
- 你會沒事的 - 這可不像沒事 伙計
- You're gonna be fine! - This is not good, man!
你可以的大塊頭 加油啊 彼得
You got this, big guy! Here we go, Peter!
- 我們是X特攻隊 對嗎？
Look at me. We're X-Force, right?
- 我們是X特攻隊！- 我們是X特攻隊！
- Yeah, we're X-Force. - We're X-Force.
我操你媽啊 什麼鬼
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
去你媽的強酸嘔吐物
Fucking acidic vomit!
哦我的天 我剛吐在自己面具裡了
Oh, God! I'm gonna throw up in my mask.
好了 我在押運車上方了
Okay, I'm over the convoy.
剩下的隊員都是在哪降落的
Where did the rest of the team land?
有好消息和壞消息
Good news and bad news.
壞消息是 隊伍全滅了
Bad news is the whole team is dead.
好消息是
The good news is,
我不覺得會有人懷念碎星
I don't think anyone's gonna miss Shatterstar.
他就是個刺兒頭 但是保羅
He was a bit of a prick. Oh, but Paul!
彼得
Peter!
彼得 我們會最懷念他
Peter, I'm gonna miss him most.
但是隱形人
But there is a slight chance
還有一點點希望
Vanisher could make it.
沒  沒希望了 他死了
- -Nope, no chance. He's dead.
整個隊伍都沒了
The whole team?
只是那些主力軍而已 我們還好
Only the main ones. We're still good.
靠 你是真傻
Fuck, you are dumb.
即使過了這麼久 我還是不無法提起這件事情
Even after all this time, I still can't talk about it.
誰知道風會這麼大
Who knew these winds would be so strong?
所有人 所有在直升機上的人
Everyone! Everyone on the helicopter!
和所有不在直升機上的人
And everyone not on the helicopter!
他們往隧道去了
They're headed into the tunnel.
我是那孩子的全部希望了
I'm that kid's only hope,
所以坐穩了 等我指揮
so sit tight and wait for my word.
無所謂
Whatever.
反正我們也救不回來了 我要下去了
We're gonna lose 'em. I'm dropping in.
真是太悲觀 唯一的幸存者
Uh, that's a negative, sole survivor.
幸運不是超能力 我們完蛋了
Luck is not a superpower! We are so fucked!
不 我們絕對沒完蛋
No, we most certainly are not fucked.
真的假的 我不明白
Seriously, I don't get it!
怎麼 你會從眼睛裡射出幸運激光嗎
What, you shoot luck lasers out of your eyes?
很難想像的啊
It's just it's hard to picture.
一點都沒有電影感
And certainly not very cinematic.
說真的 幸運
I mean, luck?
就是一群 嗑藥嗑嗨的
What coked out, glass pipe-sucking
怪胎漫畫家
freakshow comic book artist...
想出來的狗屎東西嗎
came up with that little chestnut?
可能是個連腳都畫不出來的家伙
Probably a guy who can't draw feet!
再說一遍 責任都在我的肩上了
Once again, it all falls on my shoulders.
我簡直就是中了不得不做主角的詛咒
It's why I'm cursed to be a solo act.
- 為什麼... - 我進來了
- Wander the Earth... - I'm in.
不好意思 你剛說什麼
I'm sorry, what did you say?
我進來了
I'm in.
你他媽怎麼這麼快就進去了
How in the fuck are you in already?
- 哦 該死
Oh, shit.
電鎖 十二點鐘方向
It's Cable. 12 o'clock.
新計劃 用上你全部的假像出的超能力
New plan. Use all of your imaginary powers
阻止電鎖殺死那孩子
to stop Cable from killing that kid.
我在你六點鐘方向
I'm coming up on your six.
這槍真是酷炫
That gun is amazing!
嘿 混蛋
Hey! Asshole!
他在哪 我看不到他了
Where is he? I can't see him.
他在你上面
He's on top of you.
他要從後面進去了
He's going in through the back!
哦天哪 他進去了
Oh, God, he's inside!
你知道你在說什麼對吧
You hear yourself, right?
一不小心雙關了
Accidental double entendres!
- 羅素 羅素·柯林斯
Russell! Russell Collins!
放過那孩子 約翰·康納
Hands off that kid, John Connor!
不 不 不
No, no, no!
媽的
Shit!
兩個人才能好好玩
Two can play that game!
抓到了 不對 沒抓到
Got it! No, I don't.
看你的了 媽媽
Showtime, mama!
幸運女神 接過方向盤吧
Lady Luck, take the wheel.
我本想問問你是誰 不過你馬上就要死了
I'd ask who you are, but you'll be dead in a second.
我是多米諾 並不覺得會死
I'm Domino, and doubtful.
堅持住啊 小多
Hang in there, Doms!
這麼開真的好難啊
Oh, this is really hard.
你把我的滑雪球游戲幣還給我
And give me back my Skee-Ball token.
- 你干得不錯  - X特攻隊
- You're doing great. - X-Force.
我猜重音回響死不了
I guess dubstep never dies.
你殺了布萊克（黑人）·湯姆 你個種族歧視的混蛋
You killed Black Tom, you racist son of a bitch!
這運氣可不太好啊
That's unfortunate.
我們剎車壞了
We got no brakes!
自己想辦法
Figure it out!
沒有什麼是我殺不了的
There's nothing I can't kill.
哥還會空手道呢
Somebody knows karate.
放馬過來吧 獨眼威利
Give me your best shot, One-Eyed Willy.
我來了
Here we go.
多米諾 你介意開慢點嗎
Domino, mind slowing us down?
我什麼壞事都沒干啊
Here goes nothing.
敲啊敲
Knock, knock.
這才是好孩子
That's my boy.
哦 天啊
Holy...
我得承認...
I'll be first to admit...
這跟原先計劃的不一樣
this did not go according to plan.
我還要承認的是
I'll also be the first to admit that
那個計劃是用蠟筆寫的
that plan was written in crayon.
看起來羅素好像交了個新朋友
Looks like Russell found a new friend. Jelly.
原來多米諾也是有點牛逼
Turns out Domino's a bit of a badass,
還有或許 可能 有一點小幸運
and maybe, possibly mildly lucky.
但電鎖 這家伙現在有點小情緒
But Cable? Ugh. That guy's in a mood.
一點馬上
A mood that is
就會變得超級糟糕的小情緒
about to get significantly worse.
我的身體好像非常不對勁啊
Something is so terribly, terribly wrong.
哦天哪 疼死我了
Oh, God, that hurt.
羅素
Russell.
Russell!
你在哪裡
Russ, where are ya?
羅素 你還好嗎
Russell. Russell, you're okay!
太好了 感謝上.. 我的天哪
Oh, thank God. Oh, my God!
紅坦克
Juggernaut!
我就知道是你
I thought that was you!
我應該穿白內褲出門的
I should've worn my white pants.
你可能會經常聽別人對你說這個 但我是你的忠實粉絲
You probably get this a lot, but I am a huge fan.
《非凡X戰警》第183期 《雷神索爾》第411期
Uncanny X-Men 183. Thor 411.
《X戰警無限》第1卷12期
X-Men Unlimited 12.
在你衝過來殺我的時候
You know, it has always been a dream of mine...
看著你頭盔上倒映出我的臉
to see my face reflected in your helmet...
是我一直以來的夢想
as you charge at me with murderous intent.
我不是說現在
I don't mean right now.
我現在要把你撕成兩半
I'm gonna rip you in half now.
這是典型的紅坦克台詞
That is such a Juggernaut thing to say.
哦天哪 我感覺不到我的雙腿了
Oh, my God! I can't feel my legs.
我感受不到...
I can't feel...
哦 他們就在這
Oh, no, they're right here.
沒事了 找到了 羅素
Got 'em. God, Russell.
我肩負著一個使命
I have a mission.
就是復仇
To get my revenge.
我要活活燒死那個校長
I'm going to burn that headmaster alive.
你不是那種記仇的類型
You're not the revenge type.
聽朋友一句
Take it from a friend.
朋友 你生病的時候是我在照顧你
Friend? You were sick, and I protected you.
你自己說的
You said it yourself.
我不是你的朋友 找個更厲害的人
"I'm not your friend. Find someone stronger."
所以我找了
So I did.
羅素 我之前沒辦法保護你
Russell, I couldn't protect you back then.
但是我現在可以了 你想讓我說些什麼呢
But I can now. What do you want me to say, huh?
說"我在乎你"嗎？ 那就對了
"I care about you"? 'Cause goddamn it,
我真的在乎你 羅素
I care about you, Russell.
紅坦克有什麼是我沒有的
What's Juggernaut got that I don't have?
別跟我說是腿 我就知道你要說腿
Don't you say legs! I know you're gonna say legs!
- 腿 -  雖然知道了 但是說出來很是很傷人
- Legs! - Still hurts to hear out loud!
這是啥 這啥... 這都不是根真的繩子
What is that? That's not a real rope!
你給我過來 年輕人
You get back here, young man!
小多
Doms!
小多 帶我離開這裡
Doms, get me out of here, please.
把我的手臂當做背包肩帶
Use my arms as backpack straps.
也許我們找到上天
I think we may have found
讓你加入我們的理由了
your cosmic reason for being here.
絕對不是這樣的原因
I'm pretty sure this isn't it.
X特攻隊
X-Force.
沒有無可救藥的孩子
No child is hopeless.
千萬別放棄那個男孩
Don't give up on the boy.
他怎麼就 這麼走了呢
How could he just walk away?
他眼睛裡都是冷漠
It was the coldness in his eyes.
你真該去聽聽他說的那些話
You should've heard it.
原來家庭真的是句髒話
I guess family really is an F-word.
媽媽 幫我揉揉腿好嗎
Rub my legs, Mama.
我為什麼要幫你揉腿？
Why would I rub your legs?
求你了 好痛啊 重新長腿越來越痛了
Please, they hurt. I have growing pains.
這他麼...
What in the...
為什麼你的手又這麼小了
Why is your hand so tiny again?
那不是我的手
That's not my hand.
啊我的天媽呀
Oh! Mary, mother of Joseph!
對我來說還是不錯的
That was nice for me.
韋德 我聽說了押運車隊發生的事 還有
Wade! I heard what happened with the convoy and...
你為什麼不把那東西遮起來
Why wouldn't you cover that up?
一個戰士沒有什麼好羞愧的
A warrior has nothing to be ashamed of.
話是沒錯 可是你有啊 看看你
Yeah, but you do. Look at you.
你就大咧咧的這麼敞著嗎
You're just straight shirt-cocking it,
嬰兒學步風
toddler-style.
哦 是啊 就像小熊維尼
Oh, yeah. Full Winnie the Pooh.
到底發生了什麼事 和我說說
The hell's happening? Describe it.
如果我是你的話 我是不會讓他說的
I wouldn't ask him to do that, if I were you.
- 就像是... - 開始了
- It's like, um... - Here we go.
他就像是在用肛門生小孩
It's like he was giving birth anally,
但是半途而廢了
but they quit halfway through.
他們先讓腿出來了 然後他們說
They got the legs out, and they said,
你猜怎麼著 我不干了
"You know what, I'm done."
滿意嗎
Happy?
從腰部以下他就像個木偶
It's like he's a Muppet from the waist down.
只是這一次
But this time, you can see
你能看見木偶的雞雞
the Muppet's dick.
天吶 他雞雞的尺寸有點...
Grover's got a cock the size of a twig.
黃鼠狼先生 我不能並排停車了
Mr. Weasel, I can no longer be double-parked.
我已經收到三張罰單了
I've had three tickets already.
不不不 老侍 不要再來一次啊
No, no, no, DP, not again!
這事以前也發生過嗎
This has happened before?
天吶 吐還是不吐
- -Jesus! Either vomit or don't.
這個決定糾結死我了
The indecision is killing me.
為什麼上帝不把我的聽覺也一起帶走
Why couldn't God take my hearing?
哇哦
Oh. Wow!
別激動 他們會長回來的
Cool your pits. They're growing back.
我說的是你的臉
I'm talking about your face.
我從來沒有見到過你不帶面具的樣子
I've never seen you without your mask before.
- 天吶  - 看起來像個鱷梨
- Jesus Christ! - Looks like an avocado.
- 不過你的腿 有點可愛
Your legs, though, they're cute.
你想借條褲子嗎
You wanna borrow a pair of pants?
我很高興大家都來了
I'm glad everybody dropped by.
你們一定很想好奇為什麼我不叫你們過來
You must be wondering why I didn't call you here.
我來告訴你為什麼我會在這裡
I'll tell you why I'm here.
時間旅行者妻子的老公
"The Time Traveler's Wife's" husband...
在我生命的某一刻擊敗了我
beat me within an inch of my life.
他一直折磨我
He was torturing me!
但是我只告訴了他 所有他想知道的事
But all I told him was everything he wanted to know.
所以 我來這裡是幫大家做好准備
So, I'm here to help us gear up.
這樣你們就可以不用帶我一起去追殺他了
So we can go after him without me.
不
No!
我要單打獨鬥
I'm doing this alone.
紅坦克
The Juggernaut
- 會把你們都殺了 - 行吧
- will kill you all. - Fair enough.
- 我只是需要幾個小時
I just need a couple of hours to get some legs
- 讓我的腿恢復  - 你打算怎麼做
- under me. - What will you do?
我不在乎那個小孩對我做了什麼
I don't care what the kid did to me.
我也不會讓電索抓到他
I ain't letting Cable get to him,
即使我不得不讓他舔陰囊舔到死
even if I have to teabag him to death.
這個時候來說 的確只是喝口茶的事
It's really just a sip of tea at this point.
閉嘴 黑人黑寡婦 我現在文思如泉湧
Zip it, black Black Widow! I'm flowing.
第一件要做的事就是
The first order of business is
把我送到電索面前
to get me in front of Cable...
這樣我就能把他身上的血全放了
so I can pull all the fucking blood out of his body...
然後把他的骨頭弄成節假日首飾
and fashion his bones into holiday jewelry.
然後我要把他的皮
Then, I'm gonna take his skin...
用它拿來完成我們自制的交配鼓
and stretch it out over a homemade mating drum.
他正站在你背後面 對吧
He's standing right behind you, isn't he?
這都是什麼破事
What in the ass?
這公寓是掛在Tinder上了嗎 還是Grindr
Is this apartment listed on Tinder? Grindr?
來這惹事 你可挑錯地方了 未來小子
You picked the wrong shithole to fuck, future boy.
有必要這樣嗎
Ugh. Is that really necessary?
不 那是他本能
No. It's his "Basic Instinct."
我們能為你做點什麼嗎
What can we help you with?
我是來給你提建議的
I'm here to proposition you.
我的天
Oh, boy!
他真的把事情搞砸了 不是嗎
He's really teeing it up, isn't he?
誰來開第一個玩笑
Who gets to make the first joke?
我覺得我們應該同時開槍打他
I think we should all do it at the same time.
好主意
Good call.
我打賭45美元 你爛透...
For $45, you get sucky-suck.
我只跟穿了褲子的人來 傻叉
I only do over the pants, mouth stuff.
我去
Fuck!
我的提議是 有個蓋·皮爾斯的
The Proposition has a wonderful
精彩表演
Guy Pearce performance.
等等 等等 等等 我想重新說一次我的
Wait, wait, wait! I wanna do mine over.
- 再給我們開個頭唄 - 我需要你幫忙
- Give us the line again. - I need your help!
相信我 對於這種情況 我比你更不開心
Trust me, I'm even less happy about this than you are...
但是你放走了紅坦克 你個蠢貨
but you unleashed the Juggernaut, you dumb cunt!
我沒法一個人干掉他
I can't bring him down alone.
所以就是這樣
So here we are.
遺憾的是 我們不再接受
We're no longer accepting applications
X特攻隊的申請了
for X-Force, unfortunately.
就算我們還收
Even if we were...
現在還有暴風預警
there's a wind advisory in effect until at least...
我們沒多少時間了
We don't have a lot of time.
你的朋友快要拿到他首殺了
Your friend's about to make his first kill.
無意冒犯 但是既然你知道這麼多
No offense, but if you know so much...
為什麼不回到他還是個孩子的時候殺了他呢
why not travel back to when he was a baby, kill him then?
或者干脆 再回遠一點
Or better yet, head back a little further,
殺掉希特勒寶寶
kill baby Hitler.
我用的這種穿梭時間的設備
I use a device to slide through time.
我回去得越久就越難控制
The longer I travel, the harder it is to control.
我只有兩個能源板 一個送我過來
I got two charges: one to get me here,
另一個送我回家
one to get me home.
你還真是輕描淡寫
That's just lazy writing.
羅素今晚會去殺
Your boy's gonna kill the headmaster
孤兒院的院長
of the orphanage tonight.
從這之後 他就會嘗到殺人的甜頭
After that, he gets a real taste for it.
就像是十歲的克爾斯滕·鄧斯特 狗日的
Like 10-year-old Kirsten Dunst, motherfucker!
然後他就會不停的
So he keeps killing...
殺啊殺 殺啊殺
and killing, and killing,
一直殺
and killing.
直到有一天 他殺了不該殺的人
Until one day, he kills the wrong fucking people.
我的人
My people.
別緊張
Relax.
我只是從我的雜物包裡拿點東西
I'm retrieving something from my utility bag.
你明知道這是個芬妮包
It's a goddamn fanny pack...
你這個變態的小婊子
and you know it, you sick son of a bitch!
這區別簡直就是天上地下
The difference is night and day.
你讓我想起了我的妻子
You remind me of my wife.
你說什麼
I'm sorry.
我說 你讓我想起了我的
I said, "You remind me of my wife."
不 我的意思是
No, I'm sorry that you said that...
你為什麼邊塗唇膏邊含情脈脈地看著我 然後說出這種話
while making heavy eye contact and applying lip balm.
她日子過得總是很坎坷
She always struggled.
但是她很風趣
But she was funny...
她總是用幽默濾掉她的痛苦
and filtered her pain through the prism of humor.
這是我永遠都做不到的事
Something I could never master.
她的死全都是因為我
It was my fault she died.
我的工作是阻止像他一樣的人
It was my job to stop people like him.
我好幾次都差點得手了
I came close a few times.
他因此很不開心
He wasn't too happy about that.
他一直試圖傷害我
He was trying to hurt me...
並且他很清楚該如何才能傷害到我
and he knew exactly how to do it.
被我治愈的怪胎
Blessed are the wicked
都是上帝賜福
who are healed by my hand.
他來到我家裡
He came into my home...
並奪走了把那地方變成家的唯一理由
and took the only thing that made it a home.
聽起來耳熟嗎
Sound familiar?
對不起
- I'm sorry. - Uh-huh.
不 我是真的抱歉
No, I'm really sorry.
但那個不是羅素
But that isn't Russell.
- 他不是非得變成那樣 - 如果你像我一樣的了解他的話...
- It doesn't have to be him. - If you knew what I knew...
是 他是脾氣不好
Yeah, he's got anger issues...
也許還有點學習障礙
maybe a small learning disability...
一點肥胖症
splash of diabetes...
但沒有什麼是不能被解決的
but nothing that can't be fixed.
如果你可以回到過去
If you could go back...
阻止那些殺死你女友的人 你會去嗎
and stop the people that took your girl, would you?
廢話 我他媽當然會
Of course I fucking would!
但我不會去殺一個孩子
But I wouldn't kill a kid.
我沒有叫你去殺他
I'm not asking you to kill a kid!
我會殺了他
I'll kill the kid.
我是在叫你去拯救其他的幾百個孩子
I'm asking you to save hundreds of other kids.
羅素會燒光那家孤兒院
Russell's gonna burn down that orphanage.
我想你那去世的女友
And I can imagine your dead girlfriend...
也想看到你去做正確的事情 對吧
would want you to do the right thing, wouldn't she?
所以你考慮得怎麼樣 帥哥
So, what's it gonna be, handsome?
給我個機會去救他
Give me a chance to save him.
- 什麼 - 你說過的
- What? - You said...
一旦他殺了人 就會嘗到甜頭
once he kills someone, he gets a taste for it.
如果我們可以在那之前阻止他
If we can get to him before that happens...
答應我你會給我個機會
promise you'll give me a chance
把他帶到另一條路上去
to put him on a different path.
你要什麼機會
Define "chance."
我不知道 拯救一個人的靈魂
I don't know. How long does it take
要多久？ 根本也沒法算...
to save someone's soul? That's not...
- 我給你三十秒
I'll give you 30 seconds.
- 什麼？ 不夠啊 - 就能給你這麼久
- What? No! - Best I can do.
愛要不要
Take it or leave it.
他學會走路了
He's doing it!
看看這個小家伙 他做到了
Look at the little fella. He's doing it.
他走過來了
There he goes.
我的天吶
Jesus Christ!
敞著穿襯衫到處晃屌地走過來
Just shirt-cocking it.
你可以的 小伙計
There you go, little fella.
加油 你能做到的
Go on, you're doing it!
你個漂亮 沒毛 扭扭腿的小寶貝
My beautiful, hairless, Twizzler-legged baby boy.
天哪
Christ!
真夠惡心的
That's disturbing.
三十秒
30 seconds.
- 成交 - 成交
- Deal. - Deal.
我完全不知道發生了什麼
I have no idea what's happening.
看不到最好
Probably for the best.
這就是 你為什麼從來不吃生海星
And that is why you never eat a raw starfish.
這只是常識
It's just common sense.
我們這他媽是在去哪
Where the hell are we going?
你自己說的
You said it yourself.
沒人打得過紅坦克 我們需要後援
Nothing can stop the Juggernaut. We need backup.
我會沐浴在你敵人的血液裡
I will bathe in the blood of your enemies.
你能關掉音樂嗎
Can you turn off the music?
不准你關
You'll do no such thing.
你干嘛不直接用印度口音說呢
Why don't you just say it in an Indian accent?
你他媽在說什
What the hell are you...?
再一次 你這醜腦袋裡只有思維狹隘
Once again, intolerance rears its ugly head.
真對不起 會好起來的
I am so sorry. It gets better.
我他媽才不是種族主義者 你這白痴
I'm not a fucking racist, moron!
跟黑湯姆說去吧 他像我兄弟一樣親
Tell that to Black Tom. He was like a brother to me.
這一點我跟這個老白人站一隊
I'm with the old white guy on this one.
這可是個反差萌哦
And that's a twist.
所以你在未來
So what exactly do you
究竟是干什麼的啊 恩？
do in the future, anyway, huh?
某種士兵？
Some kind of soldier?
對 差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
我曾是一名軍人 特種兵
I was a soldier. Special Forces.
我賭五十塊 50年後的今天 我們是好兄弟
I bet 50 years from now, we're bestest buddies.
50年之後 你已經死得透透的了
50 years from now, you're very dead.
你們這一整代人把這個星球搞得亂七八糟的
Your entire generation fucked this planet into a coma.
嘣
Boom!
劇透警告
Spoiler alert.
嘖嘖 星球啊
Planets.
下次  叫優步
Next time, Uber.
給你一個劇透警告
Here's a spoiler alert.
你根本就不是什麼英雄
You're not a fucking hero.
你只不過是一個打扮成性玩具的煩人小醜
You're just an annoying clown dressed up as a sex toy.
那麼我告訴你
Well, I got news for you.
我的心放在了正確的地方
My heart is in the right place.
羅素不會殺害任何人
Russell's not gonna kill anyone.
因為我 他將會知道真愛長什麼樣
Because of me, he's gonna know what real love looks like.
多虧你 我也知道了
Because of you, I'll always know
有小睪丸的大老爺們長什麼樣
what a grown man with baby balls looks like.
我是在長大呢 不是暴露狂
I'm a grower, not a shower.
我真該讀完大學
I should've finished college.
就是這裡
Right here!
我已經犯了很多錯誤
I made mistakes!
我想彌補我的過錯
I wanna take them back!
你信任過我 我接過你的信任
You trusted me. I took that trust...
把它變成了機場廁所的
and turned it into a glory hole
尋歡洞
in an airport bathroom.
明尼阿波利斯的那個 你知道那個的
The one in Minneapolis. You know the one.
鋼力士
Colossus!
不到生死關頭 我是不會請你幫忙的
I wouldn't ask for your help unless it was life or death!
那個孩子需要我們的幫助
That kid needs our help!
我知道你在聽
I know you're listening!
他和紅坦克組隊了
He's teamed up with the Juggernaut!
那可是紅坦克啊
The Juggernaut!
我最喜歡的漫威人物沒有之一啊
That's like my favorite Marvel character ever,
但是你最好和你的英雄永不相見
but you should never meet your heroes...
因為講真 他就是個臭屌
because, honestly, he's a bit of a dick!
像很多臭屌一樣 他真的是硬如磐石
And like a lot of dicks, he's as hard as a rock...
而且只會惹麻煩
and causes nothing but problems!
- 嘿 韋德   - 嘿 雪緒
- Hi, Wade! - Hi, Yukio!
別搭理他
Please don't.
你們真是超級可愛的一對呢
You guys make a super cute couple.
我說到哪了？ 哦 想起來了
Yeah. Where was I? Oh, yeah!
鋼力士 聽著
Colossus! Look, I don't deserve
我不配做你的朋友更不配獲得你的幫助
your friendship or your help.
但這個孩子需要你的幫助
But this kid does.
而且我不像其他人那樣放棄他
And I'm not gonna bail on him like everyone else.
噢 別這樣
Oh, come on!
鴿子翅膀那貨有可能會來幫忙嗎？
Any chance Pigeon Wings is available?
來不來都沒關系 不幫忙也沒事的
That's just fine! That's fine!
但 你知道嗎
No! You know what?
做正確的事情有時會很糟糕很混亂
Doing the right thing is sometimes messy...
而且特別不方便
and fucked up, and not particularly convenient!
所以你就待在這兒吧 待在這個該死的處女堡裡
So stay here in Chateau de Virgin...
我們會他媽的繼續前進
while we go get our fuck on!
你做的很棒
You're doing great.
你戴這頭盔是因為
So you wear that helmet because
你兄弟想要讀你的心？
your brother tries to read your mind?
是的 不過他現在坐輪椅了 所以我跟他互不相欠了
Yeah, but he's in a wheelchair, so even-steven.
有人來了 先生 是羅素
Someone's coming. It's Russell, sir.
他不是一個人來的
He's not alone.
保護好孩子們
Secure the children.
我們去大鬧一場 你覺得怎樣？
What do you say we go fuck some shit up?
大鬧一場 是我合法的中間名
"Let's fuck some shit up" is my legal middle name.
幫我擋著後面 我去對付那個老家伙
Watch my back. I've got the old man.
祝你好運 兄弟
Amen, brother.
是時候見一見墨西哥炸卷餅了
Time to make the chimichangas.
30秒
30 seconds.
我終於知道我為什麼會在這裡了
I finally know why I'm here.
我在這個地方長大的
I was raised in this place.
不過...不是被撫養大的 是一路被折磨過來的
Well, not raised. I was tortured.
原來老天爺讓你來這是這個原因啊
Wow! It's your cosmic reason for being here.
- 我可以開始了嗎 - 一定會很好玩
- Shall we? - This is gonna be fun.
嘿 一直想問你 那個
Hey! Been meaning to ask you...
詭異的髒兮兮的流浪熊玩偶是什麼玩意
what's with the creepy, dirty hobo bear?
那不是污垢 那是我死去女兒的血
It's not dirt. It's the blood of my dead daughter.
我有谷蛋白敏感
I have a gluten sensitivity.
一杯紅酒就能讓我.... 撲...
So one glass of wine, I just...
對
Yeah.
希望我們還能回到過去
Wish we could head back in time,
把那些都扳正
and I could take all that back.
我們應該直接放音樂
We should just cue the music.
歡迎回家 羅素 我們很想你
Welcome home, Russell. We missed you.
羅素！
Russell!
你不需要這樣做 我們談談吧
You don't need to do this! Let's talk!
你為什麼穿的像大學炸彈客？
Why are you dressed like the Unabomber?
原來是這樣
That's why!
早說過這小雜碎已經沒救了
Told you this little fucker's too far gone.
閉嘴 滅霸 我們商量好的 你...
Zip it, Thanos! We have a deal and you fuck...
嘿！
Hey!
我要把那個出租車司機塞到你屁股裡
I'm gonna shove that cab driver right up your ass.
我現在渾身無力
My body and my hands are so soft.
你也許應該回車上
You should probably head back to the car.
我也覺得我應該回車上
I think I'll head back to the car.
你要扣動扳機 槍才有用
It works best when you pull the trigger.
你的槍真牛逼
That gun is amazing!
說啊！
Say it!
你這個令人憎惡的人！
You are an abomination!
這次我要把那個紅色的家伙塞進那個老東西裡
Now, I'm gonna shove the red guy up the old guy.
我信了 大家顧好自己吧！
I believe him! Every man for themselves!
抓到了！
Gotcha!
滾一邊去 小矬子
Beat it, midget!
你還好嗎 大塊頭？太陽快要落山了
Hey, big guy, the sun's getting real low!
啊 操操操要屎了
Oh, shit fuck!
過來吧 小美人
Come here, beautiful.
說啊!
Say it!
你來幫我了
You came for me.
我不會放棄你
I'm not giving up on you,
你也不要放棄那個男孩
and you are not giving up on that boy.
是誰說規矩是不能破壞的？
Who says that rules aren't meant to be broken?
是時候下黑手了
It's time to fight dirty.
是時候掃蕩全場了 強尼
Time to sweep the leg, Johnny.
要打就跟哥打 別欺負弱小
Hey! Pick on someone your own size!
真像是你說的話
That's such a you thing to say!
去干掉他吧 小老虎！
Go get him, tiger!
動畫特效大戰即將登場
Big CGI fight coming up!
他沒問題的
He's doing great.
說啊！
Say it!
- 羅素 - 答對了！
- Russell. - Bingo!
沒錯 哥出陰招了
That's right! I'm fighting dirty!
好極了
Oh, great!
他們在這 這幫怪物
There they are! Those freaks!
一幫披著護工皮的武裝戀童癖
A bunch of armed pedophiles in nursing shoes.
- 我能拿一支這種槍嗎？
Can I have one of those guns?
- 不行 - 好吧
- No. - That's fine.
快從這裡滾出去 你們這些變種雜碎
Get off this property, mutant scum!
用這塊磚也是一樣的
I'm just gonna use this brick.
火力全開
Maximum effort.
誰說你們再也回不了家了？
Who says you can't go home again?
說啊
Say it.
說你每次折磨我時說的那些
Say what you said every time you tortured me!
說啊！
Say it!
被我治愈的怪胎都是上帝賜福！
Blessed are the wicked who are healed by my hand!
被我治愈的怪胎
Blessed are the wicked...
都是
who are healed...
上帝賜福！
by my hand.
游樂場的混蛋！
You commie motherfucker!
我的天吶 你也感覺到了嗎？
Oh, my God. Did you feel that, too?
只有最好的朋友才能一起解決戀童癖
Only best buddies execute pedophiles together.
你只有30秒 你個臭肛塞
You got 30 seconds, you jabbering butt plug!
你終於開始上道了！
Now we're getting it.
我要一輛公交車才能把你們都弄出去
I need a bus to get you all out of here.
孩子們...
Orphans.
哦 天啊
Oh, geez.
是時候為你所作的事付出代價了
It's time to burn for what you've done!
一個孩子不應該背負如此的力量
A child should not be burdened with such power!
羅素！等等！
Russell! Wait!
等等！他還沒有殺死任何人呢
Wait! He hasn't killed anyone yet!
- 你還需要什麼證據嗎？ - 你他媽的敢動手！
- What more do you need to see? - Don't you fucking dare!
他只是個孩子
He's just a kid!
時間不等人 你自己看著辦吧
Tick, tock. Meter's running!
我要把你熔了 然後做成一個雞巴環
I'm gonna melt you down and make a cock ring.
- 我告訴過你們！不要管我！- 來吧
- I told you! Leave me alone! - Come on!
聽我說
Listen to me!
在蘇聯的時候
That's how we do it
我們就是這樣做的
in Mother Russia.
他們說00後是最難懂的
They say millennials are the hardest to reach.
你真是做的太棒了
Oh, no. You're doing amazing.
該死 做一回壞人感覺真好
Damn, it feels good to be a gangsta!
回家吧 韋德
Go home, Wade!
你把一切都搞砸了
You're ruining everything!
我真是越來越擅長這個了
I'm getting good at this shit.
快走走走走走！
Go, go, go!
他今晚死定了 韋德
He dies tonight, Wade.
你攔不住我的
You can't stop me!
他甚至連逃跑都像個變態
He even runs like a fucking pervert.
像個丟了筆記本電腦的網絡戀童癖
Like an online predator who lost his laptop.
那槍裡還剩一顆子彈
There's one bullet left in that gun.
等等等等 等我一下
Wait, wait, wait! Please, just give me a second!
我能做到的
I got this.
- 羅素 - 往後退 回家吧  韋德
- Russell! - Stay back! Go home, Wade!
我們談談 事情不必鬧到這個地步
Let's talk. It doesn't have to go this way!
那坨屎
That piece of shit...
他的確需要為他對你做的事付出代價
he deserves to die for what he did to you.
他傷你傷的那麼重 讓你想要傷害其他人
He hurt you badly. Makes you wanna hurt others.
但如果你殺了他 他就贏了
But if you kill him, he wins.
你會成為他口中描述的樣子 甚至會變得更糟
You become everything he says you are, but worse.
你只是個孩子
You're just a kid.
你並不想傷害其他人
You don't wanna hurt anyone.
你怎麼知道我不想
How do you know what I want?
因為我曾進入過你
Because I've been inside you.
感覺哪裡怪怪的
That came out wrong.
我感受過你的處境
I've been inside your shoes.
也是很令人不爽
Which is also off-putting.
這不是一個好的比喻
It's not a great analogy.
重點是
The point is...
還有人
there are people...
在這個肮髒的世界不是只有他
There are people in this fucking world...
還是會有願意好好待你的人
besides him, who will treat you right.
現在還來得及 不要這麼做
It isn't too late. Don't do it.
我不該把你丟在那裡
I never should've left you there.
我絕對不該把你丟在那
I never should've left you in that prison.
我不能相信你了
I can't trust you.
我不能相信任何人
I can't trust anybody!
太棒了  孩子
Wonderful kid.
你不能阻止我的 韋德
You can't stop me, Wade!
我還有一個主意
I got one more idea.
哪怕對我來說 這也是個很爛很爛的主意
It's just a really bad one, even for me.
韋德  你要做什麼
Wade, what are you doing?
好了 這個是我之前那麼冷漠對你的懲罰
All right. This is for all the marbles, kid!
你今天會殺掉某個...
You're gonna kill someone today...
被我治愈的怪胎
Blessed are the wicked...
那就是我了
...then it's gotta be me.
都是上帝賜福！
...who are healed by my hand!
操他丫的
Fuck this!
告訴我 他們這個拍成慢鏡頭了
Tell me they got that in slow motion.
這感覺不太妙啊
Oh, that's not good.
不是吧
No, sir.
你為我  犧牲了你自己
You sacrificed yourself for me.
是啊
Yeah.
這是我做過的做好的事了
And it was the best thing I ever did.
我說過我很關心你的
I told you I care about you.
羅素  你是個好孩子
You're a good kid, Russell.
嗨
Hey.
看那只熊
The bear.
起作用了
It worked.
因為你
Because of you.
不 韋德 是因為你
No, Wade, because of you.
住手 住手 住手
Stop, stop, stop!
住手
Stop!
別救我 就讓我這樣走吧 好嗎？
Just let it happen, okay?
我猜我的心終於在正確的地方了
I guess my heart was finally in the right place.
這個謎題真是太難解了
That riddle is so fucked up.
我很抱歉 我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
千萬別 千萬別
Don't be. Don't be.
我很久之前就想這樣了
I've been trying to make this happen for a while.
所以 不要離開我
Please, just don't leave me.
我不希望死的時候沒有人送送我
I don't wanna die without an audience.
我們哪裡也不會去
We are not going anywhere.
啊 天哪 我希望奧斯卡評委看著呢
Oh, God, I hope the Academy is watching.
好好休息吧
Just rest, okay?
爸爸？
Papa.
你能聽到我嗎
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
在我走之前 抱歉...
Before I go...
抱歉 我還有幾口氣兒
Sorry, I got a bit more in me.
多米諾
Domino.
我想把我的冒險時光表 留給你
I want you to have my Adventure Time watch.
聽起來我是那個幸運兒
Turns out that I'm the lucky one.
謝謝
Thank you.
嗨 叫塞布麗娜的年輕女巫
Hey, Sabrina, the Teenage Witch.
很高興認識你
It has been a pleasure.
- 嗨 雪緒 - 嗨 韋德
- Hi, Yukio. - Hi, Wade!
對... 還有你
And you...
鉻合金骨頭
Chrome Bone.
我一直都不是一個很好的朋友
I haven't always been the best friend to you.
但你一直都是我很好的朋友
But you've always been that to me.
所以謝謝你
So thank you.
為了我說一次"操"吧
Say "fuck" for me.
一次就好 來吧
Just once. Come on,
我們一起說 不是件很難的事
we'll do it together. It's no big deal.
開始了  123...
Here we go. One, two, three. F... F... F...
操
Fuck.
哇哦 祝你下地獄愉快 犯嘴賤的孩紙
Wow! Enjoy hell, swamp mouth.
還有你 電索
And you, Cable.
回到你的家吧 告訴他們韋德 跟他們問好
You get back to your family. You tell 'em Wade says hi.
還有答應我 答應我一件事
And promise me. Promise me one thing.
以後要根據
That you'll start judging people...
人品來評判人
not by the color of their skin,
而不是他的膚色
but by the content of their character.
- 上帝啊 - 小羅素？
- Jesus. - R-Dog?
你們來了 嘿
There you are. Hey!
你現在是超級英雄了 好老弟
You're a superhero now, bubba.
看…
Look.
家庭這個詞 不是髒話
Family is not an F-word.
好嗎
All right?
你會找到溫暖的家的
There's one out there for you.
要繼續尋找好嗎
Just keep looking, okay?
伙計們 有那麼一小會兒
Guys, for a second there...
我們已經是很棒的團隊了
we made a pretty good team.
哎 好難死啊
Oh, it's so hard to go.
好喜歡跟你們在一起啊
I just love being around you guys so much.
特別特別喜歡
So, so much.
呀 我現在能感受到了  要到了 耶
No, I can feel it now. Here it comes, yeah.
感受到了靈魂出竅…
I feel the soul exiting the husk.
你們看得見嗎
Can you see it?
你們看到那道美麗的白光了嗎?
Do you see that beautiful bright light?
就在那兒
There it is.
那個是太陽
Oh, that's the sun.
不要盯著它看
Don't stare directly into that.
我最後還想說幾個字…
I just have a few final words.
啄木鳥
Woodpecker.
牙齦炎
Gingivitis.
一派胡言
Codswallop.
你想來堆雪人嗎?
Do You Want to Build a Snowman?
對不起我遲到了
Sorry I'm late.
那會有一幫
There was a bunch
可能會摔成殘疾的孩子卡在樹上了
of handicapable children who were stuck in a tree.
不對
- No. - No.
- 不是 不過我的確幫了一個孩子 - 對
- But I did have to help a kid. - Yeah.
- 他有一個很糟糕的名字 - 特別爛
- He's got a terrible name. - It's just awful.
想告訴他來著
- Ugh. - I tried to tell him.
這兒是天堂嗎
Is this heaven?
現在是了
It is now.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
沒事的
It's okay.
我真的好想你
I missed you so much.
什麼 怎麼了
What is it? What's wrong?
時間還沒到
It's not time.
什麼叫時間還沒到
What do you mean it's not time?
我在這呢 我做到了
I'm here, I made it.
- 你不能待在這兒   - 不不不
- You can't stay. - No, no, no.
我就要留在這 沒有你我哪都不去
I'm staying. I'm not going anywhere without you.
沒關系的
It's okay.
我們會團聚的 只是不是現在
There's a time for us. It's just not now.
- 他們需要你 - 誰?
- They need you. - Who?
你的髒話
Your F-word.
為什麼
Why?
你會知道的
You'll find out.
沒事的 我會一直在這的
It's all right. I'll be here.
我愛你
I love you.
我知道 我也愛你
I know. I love you, too.
現在走吧
Now, go.
走吧 離開這裡
Go on. Go, get out of here.
走吧
Go.
喂
Hey!
像你想我一樣狠狠的親我吧 小賤
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
你過來啊
Well, come here.
別搞貓王
Don't fuck Elvis.
- 別搞鋼力士 - 什麼
- Don't fuck Colossus. - What?
是時候見見墨西哥炸卷餅了
Time to make the chimichangas.
三十秒
30 seconds.
嗨 還沒問你 你這個詭異的
Hey. Been meaning to ask you...
髒兮兮的流浪熊是怎麼回事
what's with the creepy, dirty hobo bear?
那是我女兒的泰迪熊
It's my daughter's teddy bear.
她的名字叫霍普
Her name's Hope.
哇
Well...
你干什麼呢哈哈
What are you doing?
某人准備開始搞基了呢
Somebody swiped right.
告訴我 他們把這個拍成慢鏡頭了
Tell me they got that in slow motion.
你為了我犧牲了自己
You sacrificed yourself for me.
似乎我…
It would seem I...
貨真價實的高檔鉛
Genuine, high-grade lead.
你個混蛋居然穿越時間來救我
You time-sliding son of a bitch!
你為了我這麼做的？
You did this for me?
等等 你回不去了
Wait. You can't go back.
你的燃料已經用完了
You used the last of your fuel.
你的孩子和老婆怎麼辦？
What about your girl, your wife?
沒事 我的家人很安全 還有 我這麼做不是因為你
Now, my family's safe. And I didn't do it for you.
現在 我要在這兒四處逛一會兒
No, I'm gonna stick around for a while...
確保這個世界
and make sure the world
不把自己搞成渣
doesn't shit itself into oblivion.
不 你這麼做是因為我
No. You did it for me.
不 不是
No, I didn't.
- 你就是 - 我不是
- You did. - I really didn't.
- 我敢肯定你就是因為我  - 不 我十分確定不是因為你
- Pretty sure you did. - No, I'm positive I didn't.
好吧 好吧 我們來擲硬幣 可以吧
Fine. All right, let's flip a coin. Okay?
正面朝上 你是因為我 正面朝下 你還是因為我
Heads, you did it for me. Tails, you did it for me.
我甚至都不用看 因為...你是為了我
I'm not even gonna look, because you did it for me.
你再說一遍
Say it again.
- 你是因為我才這麼做的 - 上帝啊
- He did it for me. - Jesus.
- 我們得把他的頸圈拿下來 - 別管它了 沒用的
- We must get the collar off. - Forget it. It's no use.
這些頸圈不會隨便脫下來的
These collars don't just come off.
韋德
Wade.
我有一個辦法
I have an idea.
不 不 不 不 別這麼做 求你了
No, no, no! Let's not do that. Please!
我寧可死於癌症 這真是太...
I'd rather die of cancer. Let's just...
天哪 的確有人說過 筆比劍還惡心
Oh, God! They do say the pen is grosser than the sword.
我們需要密碼
We need the code.
試試 七
Try, uh, seven?
你快歇歇吧 幸運隊長
Settle down, Captain Lucky.
不可能只有一個數字
It's not gonna be one number.
我的天哪 要不要這麼隨便啊
Oh, God, that's lazy writing.
運氣還在
I still got it.
把它放回到你的監獄錢包裡
Put that back in your prison wallet.
我不知道該怎麼感謝你
I don't know how to thank you.
但我知道如何去擁抱你
But I do know how to hug you.
- 不要 - 要的 來吧
- No. - Yes.
好好抱一個
Here we go. Bring it in.
來吧
Come on.
盆骨對盆骨
Pelvis to pelvis.
我們來大頭對大頭
Let's go tip to tip.
小頭對小頭 年輕人管這叫 "碼頭停靠"
There we go. The kids call this docking.
- 我丁丁裡是有把刀嗎
Is there a knife in my dick?
- 你丁丁裡是有把刀 沒錯 - 那就後退一點
- There's a knife in your dick. - I'm just gonna back up now.
- 是啊 - 不用來《燕特爾》那一套吧
- Yeah, yeah. - No need to go full Yentl.
假裝什麼事都沒有發生過
Gonna pretend like that never happened.
我們回家吧 羅素
Let's go home, Russell.
你們這些肮髒的變種人
All you dirty mutants
都會和這個男孩一起下地獄
are gonna rot in hell with the boy!
你們的靈魂已經無法救贖了
Your souls are beyond redemption!
讓我們來觀賞一下你的靈魂吧 變態！
Let's see your soul, perv!
不行 不行不要再來了 我們比這強多了
No, no! No! No more! We're better than that!
我們比他強多了
We're better than him!
再也沒有無意義的暴動 再也不會血流成河
No more senseless violence! No more bloodshed!
他會遭報應的
We'll let karma take care of him.
審判之日已經到了
The day of reckoning is here!
我會想他的了 他看上去還不錯
I'm gonna miss him. He seemed great.
勇氣 混蛋
Courage, motherfuckers!
還有因果 混蛋
And karma, motherfucker.
你開車來30秒之前我就聽到了
I could hear you coming the last 30 seconds.
我都差點板不住臉了
I could barely keep a straight face.
我還要更多
I want some more.
我打包票你是這麼想的 棕豹
I bet you do, Brown Panther.
我們得在艸坦克醒來之前趕緊離開
We should leave before Fuckernaut wakes up.
好主意 你要跟我們一起嗎
Good call. You guys coming with us?
不了 我得把孩子們帶回宅子裡
No, we'll get the kids back to the mansion.
再說 我們是X戰警（X男）
Besides, we're X-Men.
不對 你是X人
No, you're X-People.
你是X氣死人
You're exhausting.
我聽懂你說的了 一語雙關哈哈
I see what you did there. Puns.
- 再見 韋德  - 再見 雪緒
- Bye, Wade! - Bye, Yukio!
當你擁有
What do you get
8英尺高的鉻
when you take eight feet of chrome...
一丟丟勇氣
one pinch of courage...
一小杯好運
a cup of good luck...
一點點種族歧視
a dab of racism...
嚴重肥胖
a splash of diabetes...
和一整個手推車的癌症超晚期  你會得到什麼
and a wheelbarrow full of stage four cancer?
答案是: 家庭
Answer: a family.
你看 我說這是一部合家歡電影沒撒謊吧
See? I didn't lie what kind of film this was.
如果說你今天學到了什麼
If there's anything you take away today...
除了谷歌一下 重音回響是他媽什麼鬼
other than the need to Google, "What the fuck is dubstep?"...
那就是 我們都需要彼此陪伴
it's that we all need to belong to someone.
這麼小的玩意
How something so small generates
怎麼能產生足以讓時間倒流的能量...
enough energy to reverse time is...
別廢話了 快修吧 小11
Oh, just fix it, Eleven,
要不我就拿到天才吧去修
or I'll take it to the Genius Bar.
電鎖要是知道了 會殺了你的
Cable's gonna kill you when he finds out.
不知道你說的是誰
Never heard of him.
你以為我為什麼要幫他？
Why do you think I'm helping him?
上帝以神秘之式普降神諭
The Lord works in mysterious ways,
不是麼？ 祝你今天開心
don't I? A good day.
再見 韋德
Bye, Wade!
再見 雪緒
Bye, Yukio!
這可能不是什麼好主意
That was probably a bad idea.
我們究竟做了什麼啊？
What have we done?
我希望我們把奶酪攤鋪機刀片磨好了
I hope we sharpened the cream cheese spreader.
我很快就回來
I'll be right back!
我們孩子的名字必須得叫雪兒
We're definitely naming our kid Cher!
喔
Whoo!
彼得
Peter!
喔 X特工隊
Whoo! X-Force!
走 快走
Walk away! Just walk away!
可我們是X特工隊啊
But we're X-Force!
不 我們不是 這世界就沒什麼X特工隊
Nope! We're not, there's no X-Force!
好吧 這可夠嚇人的
All right, well, this has been pretty scary!
回家吧  甜甜熊 回家吧
Go home, Sugarbear. Go home.
好吧 你能把我郵箱地址告訴多米諾嗎？
Okay. Will you give Domino my email?
韋德 是你嗎？
Wade, is that you?
我想史崔克終於找到辦法
I guess Stryker finally
把你的嘴徹底封死了
figured out how to shut you up.
嘿 是我 別撓了
Hey! It's me! Don't scratch!
我只是在修改時間線而已
Just cleaning up the timelines!
愛你喲
Love you!
歡迎來到棒球大聯盟 小伙子
Welcome to the big leagues, kid.
不用謝我 加拿大
You're welcome, Canada.